[{"topicId":"11","id":"11000","langCode":"en","question":"rIabdp2exXJpQ4uXbD2QzXuLNF16lvXb6VeneFvlOoO9SASO8qAOtpgSkkjs0j8P+y5smZoCaOQAX68WSMJK1jyta+BViILLiDr4cmOQ6Vw\u003d","answers":["feel","have felt","feels","felt"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"fbYUV1ZLKlcp62xprJGr3MMphAhYh4qpicGGRf9y0/HM+kp/lvBEoT+m4qAj2K9df5QUAiny9MFL48HbP+Is5LGnWx6b8jz7iJm/O3TYQjgge+SmaVzmrVSuY9AHB5s76APmPzyRDnPHFGCtuRpWHn1nKVxGvo2JRVdS2rWaGfKb/cYJ9jzUo65UkkhihQjnGBBbXhbAsAC+Fh6QRSJ+/4OkCoXeyf21FB1iLqbxr7kISyjyu9hNohmWTxD6AxHgJcwJaDt43T+QWgJgkN61AoMg/3JMAWC2cRx8cn3k08uMK0bSPUUIcjqc+ty8I+jmVxWGGBSbrdwBxorns9f1Gc0/9ONIYenKIitJN906di60exksKJAw661YLV/y1V7ovn1idmRQhhHYBiwws2/4xYs5q+eklRome+6hohIuXCGANc18LoLEkHhw+s8C16BoEfUUgO5WoUpAZ6Bfhf8fPuskk1rJjmggTh+9n1/CvaJKgPTmqhrFUVTmYlziIKNnJy7uJyNEyzCLME3N7x6VYcGURqfoVjXs4fWB1T32WMn+jngbZY8z9acIoPDIBIrhDM+jWTWYe7Y4pnz2a5k/AywGtuyeBxxuYubUbMvo1LomDKw2jMUSc/VLxDDm53tOG9ujrK8M47ipnWInOElbcLDtCykY1ONp9MH8lZTB4W/d5P0pXFpiS4/g76bhT9MBcqN+sdJjiWym6l6D8R5biQ7WibvqISWwVPpvKSmmALhmy39vawBYPWG6pRnMRXn3KXX9S+dVJp+5vnP3yUnRWQrDDJ3zidJR40x6MhdkHr2M1t1T3Absj8Hv+HllJxdzy9VmbGCFUV+Rh9rsh0YwswTivEKVWTM4Wpy/riSWJwV1/zNGUX3uLgaCe0YAKj3QDcBVXYafYMDCcopcwTYirkjclVc52XFk+Kesieg3qIJ+esG6EPq/uaB6qoukPQDapgTYCxGV3oK578/gL1fwCLYVClWKbHEdV4Hs46n5qDFQ0rr/HAGSKLxNiTIjO+Bk8ZKjXxGJFCLdkPVrJvgzViEtvfGu+hPLDbTDg9/XG5GeQL5HE90l4mF8QqfXgKVeFTuP7Met84plG+J8u6mjkAxYkftj5B921X6tqOXjhUq8kWmUS879mlQHAWwlvYdlqdK5SQTfKcnpUQnhuvpT7rVVDg3Yo9ro6rngSmU6Xxk\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11001","langCode":"en","question":"GNFb5invrPJWf7CASDuclvUvnbrO3Ojx/51UTkrVChMCZhLeWvRdtvP9luN0oTCeFQdoWARIF453nCIgM1XBVA9YyBAAe7Y6T2n6WQLigtQ\u003d","answers":["took","takes","is taking","have taken"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"fbYUV1ZLKlcp62xprJGr3GgDMehpm4wVlLLnropGEDZPsxWYrROK67i4SX9JF0aolMRZ7jgEYM6JjReNnjDyDCASIS2/Sgmx5DRlmJoq9F8ASib3hZ493arr8/wUgb0KLAABPquuRIu0Ro0fy/KimL4m+qkvcMcwa7CfIpQNdggOthKi/YCb4kSDlpxT8rIK2SpXj8lwRi1SLYX8KxrmnDGNX19RCBRPw/RvmA+03/QleecKxR7HWhj/VjNmKHhhEiPmPTBBKa27jurR7NViJfvd0o4kU8njNxFihH657njUr3hLybFUx6zayfZnhRLdIDwHGJ6iK1k67v43hRlPHX1TX27OTtruGdjP7pbDuoj8qsRguW56K7ahLBRPf41/3ESeOqEBE91IUrOLBsFDdayZWejub6eFZaPoOP//GEk+gINRg1p4tw99qKD/SLRRSuA3YJWGUO/jUD1t/uWrx021T5LGGL4sx/DRFsXyl/UfFxvdgkWuGkxBRBxJ1YNSXK63DqySQnlDQQfidTWiZq5BnN8IfktUY/BymBtt7m7doprJI4teWbZGKWuPXHRdrH+sv8TeIRSGRGdefwe0C5fsKHx1qoc2kB/Qz0vwxT+FrrSstA5CIcpTn9noMUJTE0Eu++9v6w6gEzdHmNNMRuqU5zfcApVQmVRoy0pY0OkIPhEyk67OAFJ2FA1n1fKtBP5vsh47Hz+YeGqYe3XliLbNbRoAGkgsj2D8PYOs06Iab4iDlbJrSVtZhlnr7L3YONVui8+C3l1RKLi2IL3ODF2PK+UGgmeNjWY4coXVDE/Nmo9n5u2FtHrvQB4Pmnqs/sqEd1RZZWGEKLqi23Sl+2NKrb4QIXOff7OXlf/X1yBKaCGfRQWZndBpJ4IwFr5D+BYO7hO/oArwdOX8pfEbs62TNkF4NekGmPAWCufcpyVTgaCjcMKgwbe6DeQGLGfv1UkauqfHuw0s2eQ9mgjY0tfd+dxRLM9tQr0l6dHOB1nz3ILBBXWLed3+2dzpkMPAbMEHDpLUrVOsa/b3kfcCqCG5F5wR8S06FJFUTQzwKzkzizeDIJtlFvYobKKkMlFwS9vbGosI5n1eQmfGM1oMEmmVc7iA+XCTEbJjXoKXTkTRrXjiyBofj6A6B8PmjsQYiVesXajk8cdRzmEuR+GE/Q\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11002","langCode":"en","question":"WeJwoXqeN3nmopTM+7g52hEe1W81YrjQk91KleypXSJ8zuWwKw6UzMod8OvEGw1R53PmH/c5BLvKI2BMHPBwNMkWdj+VMSrCC0SnWqNs9IWw3hY97+u3QDwgyQrdKnhuKYJKAVZ/hRB6TXtn6iMQYg\u003d\u003d","answers":["have taken","take","are taking","took"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"fbYUV1ZLKlcp62xprJGr3BzscPJwXqQfGcMOJgzVrfw6JQ5sH42OvCRIHntr0b+DFKxImweN2dG7GV9CkIhvg+Xq+RgGCO5gYkKUX9Jqy4SNJlpNG9+40NAIF3Z7jKR9ihK5ybB3HlaNsqZfhk8pMlP8SywA1BvWYIQkqjjZVpxkpyGIs9D6LFTC0N4DOMhfn8+k/shAEwHQYK9XkhqpAu9bt3zDuPeiXMSVRqMJ4OizWw3WYY5KyyNzK51R4yGr/dmiOzLLJlWsOQ0ic0261gfEKpZRejdNr3IvnH3pL7GkSAS/Fwmo8c+hGW9yd+XmPz8LAcna1CZeyCfrQSNl8AhLKPK72E2iGZZPEPoDEeAleecKxR7HWhj/VjNmKHhhEiPmPTBBKa27jurR7NViJfvd0o4kU8njNxFihH657njUr3hLybFUx6zayfZnhRLdIDwHGJ6iK1k67v43hRlPHX1TX27OTtruGdjP7pbDuoj8qsRguW56K7ahLBRPf41/3ESeOqEBE91IUrOLBsFDdayZWejub6eFZaPoOP//GEk+gINRg1p4tw99qKD/SLRRSuA3YJWGUO/jUD1t/uWrx021T5LGGL4sx/DRFsXyl/UfFxvdgkWuGkxBRBxJ1YNSXK63DqySQnlDQQfidTWiZq5BnN8IfktUY/BymBtt7m7doprJI4teWbZGKWuPXHRdrH+sv8TeIRSGRGdefwe0C5fsKHx1qoc2kB/Qz0vwxT+FrrSstA5CIcpTn9noMUJTE0Eu++9v6w6gEzdHmNNMRuqU5zfcApVQmVRoy0pY0OkIPhEyk67OAFJ2FA1n1fKtBP5vsh47Hz+YeGqYe3XliLbNbRoAGkgsj2D8PYOs06Iab4iDlbJrSVtZhlnr7L3YONVui8+C3l1RKLi2IL3ODF2PK+UGgmeNjWY4coXVDE/Nmo9n5u2FtHrvQB4Pmnqs/sqEd1RZZWGEKLqi23Sl+2NKrb4QIXOff7OXlf/X1yBKaCGfRQWZndBpJ4IwFr5D+BYO7hO/oArwdOX8pfEbs62TNkF4NekGmPAWCufcpyVTgaCjcMKgwbe6DeQGLGfv1UkauqfHuw0s2eQ9mgjY0tfd+dxRLM9tQr0l6dHOB1nz3ILBBXWLed3+2dzpkMPAbMEHDpLUrVOsa/b3kfcCqCG5F5wR8S06FJFUTQzwKzkzizeDIJtlFvYobKKkMlFwS9vbGosI5n1eQmfGM1oMEmmVc7iA+XCTEbJjXoKXTkTRrXjiyBofj6A6B8PmjsQYoSXfowYHuX46b0z543xy1Q\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11003","langCode":"en","question":"25Bfb84dpVB1R6kURO0Aqlhv+SGmk8NL6glkm0X6Lhug5REHKNR1z1awYXMDNGtp/guoqwTBzJpfEe7VY/sXhVSAvsI62zeaaNO8jJscDhE\u003d","answers":["gave","have given","are giving","give"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"fbYUV1ZLKlcp62xprJGr3GgDMehpm4wVlLLnropGEDZPsxWYrROK67i4SX9JF0aolMRZ7jgEYM6JjReNnjDyDCASIS2/Sgmx5DRlmJoq9F8ASib3hZ493arr8/wUgb0KLAABPquuRIu0Ro0fy/KimPXdlAWK8ommB7NmZ1rL5LwOthKi/YCb4kSDlpxT8rIK2SpXj8lwRi1SLYX8KxrmnNKZGZ78YPixKIAqqxUobpIISyjyu9hNohmWTxD6AxHg/yElzKhjcZM15dxCtrlAaehKCfl5UJNWMG0Td3HSCVIHjYIDz5ypVo+D2hQ2XbFUbhJYhF3W+XBMKyy+xpHNBW+VjQieyN/KHpUgwX722WTXMh3ICHkwr2YMsbT5gMVURgPjkK2Zg5NWEuz6t4vHKMVdwb8EAGP1zB+j0tb1ikj8R2wADn3pPgAFXw+BTqHSLNvY4ALzfp4BPHtek7wZzn004DiePbrQPie4p7mKlg68s89I/wLPNj4ADQUeWObVAGzN8kcSbTa8aRTbD+I/lknPKAPl2a85j6D+o+VC1UJSHEiiTuquqbXAbnXVBsqBRe6Ld9t2di5MXqUnhpZg1qlrduDhmPpU5GrxnIoJYtFU34lpsM2ktXTYd0QF/1k8YFQtnowZWwyZc2IY3ylJu1zWHUQShw+DihmyIa/H20DtA6HkApb/LFYtuBJYVum8pxB0SFIX1TCRusM9x54HVP5KUwsZsIgJO2Jfmbk4s5ZdqtxQwH0l48D4dA9F8LN51sY9B8m1gfBTdCZtQ2WITLCyEkEjIiTM7/6x7kFQkJoaIHBTziBk2l15aSCd5/jEnpiYVLl90bgGxENw6ZJyyLVretVmx1KGf1I2LymtMIR+QCPUELjDXDhRNEk0gatTJNCtWj964AlgHWcY7xc3UJuXIiktCxenPHraITAZBfiY5I1TME+t/SNbeEcq8E3CUq1r1+WDKzTUWxePeS+h3rBWc9vO9+kE1krqzpMxnjwrNajSsp5uX/X+YNaWwNop0rILOvLXEHRvboWsU/XePmwUKwzEG7kUWcE+SB5XHWBGJHZDOe7fop+zmMudIFKT/ImdqZ7Mb9jPL2uhPf9i5IR9TMb0jqAOuilYN0wEV5gOpZIsTi1FvC+RsLDbNiCwqB0EOqKB6wTbj5EN1s5irQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11004","langCode":"en","question":"SOrG3G7c705o5UVtslnr9oyDdUqARS2nl0SY2a6KmOx9oG0uHwblkHYuGTatjjw1JbeogD4y0rSfo7sVSzzuT5+p8kI8UZ20AO3hg7PF1Ys\u003d","answers":["teaches","has taught","taught","is teaching"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"fbYUV1ZLKlcp62xprJGr3Ha0j2nHRi1rK5ow9YauNc1sVLTfDfCKehSH7EcqF9qLj1jefayPwIG4bHZKKh2FvBhgAIFP/cWUvmKOCQgnaydGXrH2UzSZihFcYeL7XNR7enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1/JQLuy42Z3DCMSIgoR9v8JuR4DjjCMBGhMhwwcViWndRe6Ld9t2di5MXqUnhpZg1pkdVtQpfoQTdU6ZadPXVPgKMmsMJpVF+qJU451K3bctssQYS2I+6i77O01HOm4ZQglI5QwJBieTSSPO1jcYF+/ugLM2XMKFEpGeQ+LZCVknR7zeBMk8vWvjq9C8yKR9SQh95rLY9dq+gllV95K+saqv1XVHILU1n9DCy5jfK5Pq71kRz94wvmeUKYPZ1gKfGibOny0/jk4ftBQ1ptI032CCf0Ep1F2JsupJKux1NSI7ihN2AA8J2uJOX3Ky5FGV7Xwe3lNVRY6j7R3916JUOCIQd5g/QKOarkaoGD75KSzlI1X1JPiu/eKGINZwFUPDynGrsNlyNHsIeN6crHYJcElhW4cz8m+WD+Tg+g2otM9Dm/3GCfY81KOuVJJIYoUI5xgQW14WwLAAvhYekEUifv+MhdxLWBb0yOXxF34gbT/nXgnTRnPzOAyZB2vG0InbayALMyjx6ur/qg+BIrlm14a2IdHrDaajW8rWzL5kBqKvIlisOrVRxqAWH08/X0lUVzBwjcYM+B16txYOi4+QIZe7ZP+i2RdYwQ3WIho+M7fHqV6R6RUEC1l02cJQ/XGvZmDmna3vkB/BMsLhNuJaJWe7gHVV7vfEejI3usmWb/kPYV34eRQmfDcAaLxiZYOKL4zoQZudrP2mKlhCh37/oOAMFe49ey0RCNBxRja48sk7lHlc8Z480nA9w8ebsIr6BofkwmsokezyXAb1pkxViQvqNLmhdNTWCdoFxLPzbDxg5uPg/A5gSBZ554yCNHeHAXowIx3qzb6fikigzBZATzAjN0gPA4b9CNY7eiRfT80HhRy32WX1dSIEsou+HZ7uzc6oaidi6pkS1FOzr6ktt6yc1pngI65P8sB3Cwn6TMHedaankr1KRhAUtqGRItNZRNqWJv0wUPs4G/NTFIma3QaZZeLWSSnc1so7tBwSFvBsIPegHM6JQ/we9vpDfhEKGLVVDg3Yo9ro6rngSmU6Xxk\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11005","langCode":"en","question":"utDlnHyWyOHiuj9nZcGEGNGCYZaDm8OrPLHJP/hKj3I84Ho9nG1Z2csFik0s+PY50y8fhdNyqywJd+aLJysAVFD0LuHjZ7/rcI/76h+6Iyk\u003d","answers":["is finishing","finish","was finishing","finished"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"fbYUV1ZLKlcp62xprJGr3Hjxz4NtcfBpR/rC9fjRjW7VnZQ3010r/HH+hdeh9r8CSuUDIWOgJXyWKleIjKaA2lwjyfmTlPBrVDh+7DzZNrxBEBXwcz2Ikq03SvXbqKJ3QrgMh6veFe9QYfU8RVTZ1D1c3+B5otfdrGMFFifhhoZgVC2ejBlbDJlzYhjfKUm7XNYdRBKHD4OKGbIhr8fbQAypt8VjhjaGDVTez4kehtksAAE+q65Ei7RGjR/L8qKYLLpvKRU6yPD32t/GNOhaBQhLKPK72E2iGZZPEPoDEeDwU2Y3PC1MXJ0wMWW42KDNOr31nRGeRcAkL2zQd2e6YpsPmschAGfz5zhd0gRg8zgr9/h9mlPCMncN4SN/CnGgv1q4Id24Ie0mFgUzjO9wF7ObSmNzsChOpwQrx9h2CmjxjTI1ODnaHLNjn9zJEXnuF7X4s3tQXXylvV5Zqus8X+ta//hvYY3+lKAxHBldWHg+RbCd8KJc+4L8aGdF2OU+8DN42FOdwOYy+6167kOZGYpWa/MFQbIHiq3hWdL31cMpb0wwu8x3NTNFyah0icLW8dj2AQMw6HMyaV8bKQgjWK7vCrH6uXgJURW/31V/PSQJHi+N/UU0G6SroePgHa300zo20lfs8IEGpXgQ9aH8FAtGxjtPysYUXcaBMxKoVSgR+rDXr+gGbX2+6LDOqR/8Qw/hnOTwmOoq9sLDrJNmfu7tXifz6PqBtIGc7UndhLw9x4/xco64bst254O1BrHU0YJhloObw6s8sck/+EqPcjzgej2cbVnZywWKTSz49jnTLx+F03KrLAl35osnKwBUY0itb3h+AhrObOzSdpwrqe2/WqdX8smb4AEx+qYSVc1+tLvXkmhNNwTHU+P7YEzs7RB3nfYGEx2dR2Rn98ODnd18qxmrmX7gSemp/VHZVDcGfEQcNorW+oyPp5rD0oJ+dvLGRBu6QtlIun8nqYyBWMcWzJBkkdsfOeF3f857va5kPAKQbGwu87YkYnGbGtc4l0m6+w8O9iPHqQhGwy+rfJsnwe4jBUlp5Cx+cXmhGIuoj9nAtoMWtQ9nbMmxhSMDIZjI1quDOzB2wjVOnp39Mb5nq5sXt8G44IxRk5queeLZxbhYDuGWcCqbMJMQ3F/Qih+ejFTYHtyQo4CMeGTm4WaMhB9J0kSlRV9OmDE5sUTFVTFLoLbRrR2LYZtQKoTqH/aIfjwsIap7bUgjac48YQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11006","langCode":"en","question":"xvZYel1pEo0vWWbCPOHpvdqil9xOLu03XLCNrgP6lpR+QCPUELjDXDhRNEk0gatTJNCtWj964AlgHWcY7xc3UIcpMIJSsJya0dGjwr9bFcg\u003d","answers":["have watched","watched","watch","am watching"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"fbYUV1ZLKlcp62xprJGr3FNocnVn908mE01GuHxgjB/OOlTXwbEUXk10KhDxXBEr8IPc7qS48hW07X8yny4qbH82Y4PXmxKjXL7+lPNdIWZ7O3afHeNgrYHSgZ8pIITeoDqV/ZKZ/46fMBN14ejCdm1PEHydLKpZ3uex6G6+xP9vgGKUgN+RRoh0j7+Ke1dugDzZCn300oTBq24rQ6GstghLKPK72E2iGZZPEPoDEeDwU2Y3PC1MXJ0wMWW42KDNOr31nRGeRcAkL2zQd2e6YpsPmschAGfz5zhd0gRg8zgr9/h9mlPCMncN4SN/CnGgv1q4Id24Ie0mFgUzjO9wF7ObSmNzsChOpwQrx9h2CmjxjTI1ODnaHLNjn9zJEXnuF7X4s3tQXXylvV5Zqus8X+ta//hvYY3+lKAxHBldWHg+RbCd8KJc+4L8aGdF2OU+8DN42FOdwOYy+6167kOZGYpWa/MFQbIHiq3hWdL31cMpb0wwu8x3NTNFyah0icLW8dj2AQMw6HMyaV8bKQgjWK7vCrH6uXgJURW/31V/PSQJHi+N/UU0G6SroePgHa300zo20lfs8IEGpXgQ9aH8FAtGxjtPysYUXcaBMxKoVSgR+rDXr+gGbX2+6LDOqR/8Qw/hnOTwmOoq9sLDrJNmfu7tXifz6PqBtIGc7UndhLw9x4/xco64bst254O1BrHU0YJhloObw6s8sck/+EqPcjzgej2cbVnZywWKTSz49jnTLx+F03KrLAl35osnKwBUY0itb3h+AhrObOzSdpwrqe2/WqdX8smb4AEx+qYSVc1+tLvXkmhNNwTHU+P7YEzs7RB3nfYGEx2dR2Rn98ODnd18qxmrmX7gSemp/VHZVDcGfEQcNorW+oyPp5rD0oJ+dvLGRBu6QtlIun8nqYyBWMcWzJBkkdsfOeF3f857va5kPAKQbGwu87YkYnGbGtc4l0m6+w8O9iPHqQhGwy+rfJsnwe4jBUlp5Cx+cXmhGIuoj9nAtoMWtQ9nbMmxhSMDIZjI1quDOzB2wjVOnp39Mb5nq5sXt8G44IxRk5queeLZxbhYDuGWcCqbMJMQ3F/Qih+ejFTYHtyQo4CMeGTm4WaMhB9J0kSlRV9OmDE5sUTFVTFLoLbRrR2LYZtQKoTqRUA6mWlE2dw8BeCA2EG00w\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11007","langCode":"en","question":"y2L5YiEIeibDAdysZAWkVigpX9UddSf1lflCW3b7nagAU/qqBaCfo3bpRQ4Sv3ZTK4qhCR3oUmrmyevAENJaVA\u003d\u003d","answers":["writes","wrote","was writing","has written"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"6oIc/bKGgsE9L0EOMD6TA2XefaPYJJCoqm95N0ey/Fx5T5/TGD1sWUlX0TaGnFobzClLeo882Bsgp9c4ASwEi0KPQVpEue64WYULz4fBp0xQBcr9y/ZLKMm+2CajDxwbz020ZXCutnZkfIoorssCIMrTMoBrJ/7vjz3ZQMnXl/nDbXkd0YDQ7gAfDwmLtbI/zCNjLybpvyBj16BEOsni4VWr47hwTESTvgE28qsC7QsISyjyu9hNohmWTxD6AxHgxyKx4g5G8FZBmRnUyBb3UIX+FFNJzs8/Mu53kBmLGQiBcv00iqhipyXurD2eKrLDXaMPN64fExDmd4ZL4Z14mRlQTlic+1jFmWQKMgYF/pLWwc4UIwi1qsKTwYIP5MAasfgs81Y1oLRgcRHZxxnwCCdrroX2bK8t18gfeqi8ABrHxosl5q9I20NA7HUfvfaJZD89EqEfirtA4eyUH7KwVTU8C8wEeLW0MnimjrzvRPV3oYyTd2gN1nqGTrtByrTbMh0fDP9lhjXYr4YKPNgP1Q8CSQOKT3/u5P76x/EJVfviJ4qt5/SS1bf51ge82K6SV5PJNkqTQzN0XDLWtJGO9H8Mgd6j2RUtO+EUoLToD1GX7m3/OQJrZQv1CmqcnePLVcKm6TqojHVxV6jrAC0lU9j893fKgxQD2jjuGzhjoZkI3wwoh6g1GYgahFt7ZbNkiXs0CCo9hQqdFxEBCBdfM5A9d4U1dCPMb6ChCLuNkYH8YAkt5w1WpaXT1WQ7eYp0wy8Gj8vGgqvqiovTe4C6gRojTuKgormjWgZeBXSUE70ABi9rMmeqSWtwWCXTeG/DdgiaQrkII9TSZsgrnK074O04/aQbhC5u+O0a1NRxH3n118pD0W/MofuDEkK85So+0G12XihoWebG+xsvebdnC2GtIh4jX1Es3ZAU1z2rTUGBsd/I9JLPCVT377xT6b0+inmvb5tpV4CbkkbLCFkdHj2LTwfKAk7Nb5hY4bC1SZZJ8tgt2A85+NcUSZjjAkFp9cwL+is34JtBuj8Bwd/VNZQU1TZk6rRswEA2k0cxoyyLSGUYM7X2dRvHzrmsYr+YqKeCF41M7PasccCntGbQLszE4p9ayCwe/CQhF3BnNmqn5ElYRXsfLLH7jrjP+zhg5b5uGNDBymYkBVXqN5rT4w\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11008","langCode":"en","question":"I5dalPqIa+deBpfs7gHeY+Wh/JeohVgcONFLT8ajD7ZWp/dA2nvWCbmExxqrUoPby9aj/GekRQvhTVSJf6iklw\u003d\u003d","answers":["has won","wins","was winning","won"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"fbYUV1ZLKlcp62xprJGr3JYDQcg8rrRnw4yJJTyD460iyPZmtcrcHqJo1oC/FRzmimSqaiVf8OM9nU3DlO+Kn5kQVT4wpgZY5/uYgHXXHNqpjtcoXMaunK6qFAi3y5Sh0N7eqb/+NU6NgJaz3vbNCN41z3S+e/qbUj6HD/vqLZ0ISyjyu9hNohmWTxD6AxHghyubJBWyxEXVPJKIQtZ0CRMx5Xx97KAjC+6PQUmGMSY7EjzaNWdtNkKc+klEyH+1pks7IrGkBnXASuIN4uEBpZ0+F6+lelYTIsdGg0nUT0HAiN4x1ygh2SAKABYGE70ziLp/4fUCRrNB4tek0+TcaPC1n8KtL/3XVkUwXnhYx3EQLVd7y2rElvRKTcrQRSgCCsOXR3enOITUyP7PUNrYO/9JnwUNlpepkTZuxfbCKZqdqx8T9usqp66r6e9xCbg1q1PNNFEYP5sunv256D0nMUSL7VA0FreHiAgfsONEWg+XCrQ++6NPccV++aaFLEkjhHzJGSq82EzIFpHr3EQOuKMpboey/RMR8oLgtohR/zSA2BHkW6z0slmvE5qSPchcwhHYpYUVKgOvO5v1E98xhRRKE+6MEsbtBxRIBomPNOey7NgyikbaMR756RDkNM76nNaXNGdt6ip+cYHsutLT9LJKE18Btbyy2CaLRBdDldDpp10U371I0urWkoq4TM838XsC9c2odVfhdL9TwQ1XlZNlbMhSj4/qW8xMSF59ZARE43PJoG/AUkk3lpcahQKkgUvhlgfsRsIqHD72jX4tQyAO6kgZQtIlxA0MAOq0jvvPNuwU2aERLBh4sN9Bgnv9E09sLfovNZn92ZKwp1mKiTk6fLs1pfxOpONxK/I8TE7WlMqUC//zC5bGuhNqornAFpYisd54QVo9LpkB/t7CjNyeAz3AZtTWcbQVoACoXftPYatAjp2nBUkxy/xCBfZ0FXW34qJ5GbQ0wEQ4EKmCDzu3OqlTkH0HvooGd0iSolUuSVNl6vNpPt7cDhT2m5MwZy37jqZvjaC6lCsjhBW0Apj4uetDQ6S4/vyywYltE2zyjofnG7mcSnlMBYzWX0JTWUlfi5a2T5pVwqw8IgOHmg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11009","langCode":"en","question":"VRO1xuu/ib8gccOcUR3es7Jb6I6sJZbfvrWNguNNBq3Tdp12jCWY57KFCOzu8bPNioYShf1Al0akQGC9BS85FHlkG2Qa7uK9HcUGmB9Vfs4\u003d","answers":["has held","holds","held","was holding"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"fbYUV1ZLKlcp62xprJGr3KsHLhu5VoUgU+x8cppoeSFPsxWYrROK67i4SX9JF0aolMRZ7jgEYM6JjReNnjDyDCASIS2/Sgmx5DRlmJoq9F9Cr6+2qthrsApAAiFPX2qvDtlUszI2W5+0iNIFYvCSBZw7NZbh5kMM6m+sJh4gniYxdbQCV7cL0yW36fW/G1tkNoV4BHT50pv1d7p/FtBrBd4WWHwzsPL46rNaGgvOrIEISyjyu9hNohmWTxD6AxHgWzUN8BLsY/Kc39z5MDsXdZ7tp9OVhhKd7h7a/Y170Jlz7jiZ6bmQxoh3XRYhP0BdgJEKTOY6s2Fh/gNx87R85ZPoW/iG5Iv2cXL4MHtw2BNOQ8yquqFdP9V3Udv2E+zwwvaMy5fqhM0sen7D9cmJ+RyE3HP2eW7p4E2v85zfKZ+a+/djKabxh+nrBCKJOrgf+XDVyvSPiPdKP2DYBrSQ7aXaS1+AzrLIo7OpZeGHS1k4My31o/AcG5EYKLl0AJvf6UOdskugshxqPbxOF/61B8a834ZiLFm+dQYnREJdu0bRSFfQR57Vo0fqEzBfenVs+BDz9zVclpqggRT8DAfIduYUOfI58EQEM0BrrSqAD1LBIxHjn51zWSgluOJuoyJ+EyLQAuHboIWLS6dVSbUbdNdydvjQ6LVWpctMowjo/l4T3ilrlygDxLu/vNBo0mPlNmM7cmUBwMg/cdW/tzznReFWH0rI5P8ifSF7DquMPhEBRiXMvhxuoRyCdyGRXh4KZX24/P5leu5q3vkFJeeFgODDXVodx5+MEIrQwxJ/VKlY+za8EdZAnxhZOrBX0efhuWncAZ4Vh7qWzC/SCaZ1KGVcm3mCUAdihT0lOSQ8+xBhooP+YV9dyjLpEkOQWrGmPD/35ePorG0z2RQCQ8Hon2IQyBSk1qSBX/LrYqKKWLIzg/LpDSD1r6rrnXAuqBUW2bHpd09sMInb9m4jfT+LD9hAvu9eTQJlISjipWyR74hHsKxNXlE9uDD8FxKpO+VbJL7D5Z6V2hJ8vjY46pYxcP5SUDByR9dknLwRg77Pl54lLv2SadWzIo3G87Nuf8QoPDZiPf46oaEqBGEM1AGcWtjaJHQd9zsweXcdQItJe+Q7S6p9tRV2uM9G5iGMOldA4p/0XlqNXv41lMatIAyVtQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11010","langCode":"en","question":"4UZsWMQkvAYBVjEPHMHC3z7gacLKwwjhW4dZLp11qkOYCNtRJFRygTbPPDmvTVhc","answers":["watch","watched","have watched","was watching"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"6stOUyyOtDX54FyK6i6CliBSqbMXD368mbXl1mHXREjqzGvpmLZR7aXLzwlLDLDiqg9rz8awuWCHaFvoaW8maIE3UxuwDZ4sQzCgEwBfQ1wEpeBBDUAciG5sJKBpgEHI6cajmuhb0tT/x2alhKJerN/ybNnbCXGnHImYIevQnVFyHAt9gY5CQJg+ltnX1Fb6vH8fN6ggAx9gDz8M/WOIuA7ZVLMyNluftIjSBWLwkgXq7fhsMJ08oaCEiTVj+wU1CjJrDCaVRfqiVOOdSt23LSbXTqJZAYMEPpyxarO+i+dlVt49DsQjqXzRc+r3t1S/6EoJ+XlQk1YwbRN3cdIJUlcVhhgUm63cAcaK57PX9RlBNONtOGQtP39gfEYpqJJ5RfbnN6Bog2II78oXCoNCImAhQFZPU7yjFF07galGGCVr/GWi8sVC+H3FBoppeKqnQTDJKxhx6a/k34K3dSDbeW8emudaB9goKB6mgFWxbJN18CGVlLMBuaWXa6PZ8+158VpHaVeFPp+WQyKPaiZEn0WjHwBd5BIKmjY/hj3E3XVqzelsyzpZsFYXnVXksbjh4NiFxtoETwbYHGfopJL+jcpE8bK5qqJZiWAwRPNnku3OMc0S5F3ikjqC4KQ7cbIktW4lhlZ6HhxVBttZTg3r1+It4gDkpQbRt48bY2be+enTfkchVvzIMjkVufbYSTZ/YG4fsdntY48eF2P7A2ViPr8RjsixXDhurOI3w9RivQn19F31q4NmsWvxpW01mc2HCkGYH0a23QuSy/ggU15Zm2VJPhPWaCQYsXrIClZpPIY\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11011","langCode":"en","question":"ndrJhQWrvk4nndx6V07HqjW5WjKVGpUGVMI+Zff6QJ6SYyk6jOAfaaKbMKamuIqmfdB5mVOE8tPTDKZ45nH33/KCAz8KApLSZYLnHfpLsxU\u003d","answers":["have played","played","was playing","were playing"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x11xnARJ3DQHp+QAn/pcTTvVZGcfo6VA1F0Q3GkqAIqjPsqzBtiPx7mmQFYVBtefkz6xORS/KLNHjsbik4oX4CXClF9Ickn0ocUO/0V0N6hx2RwgPdEq13NEpAZ0C4TzPAzfB+QnXxuEpEs1npRcTaarRmhkmP0pLfEJrflDZvehWgU9CnuhVLYnMmwgCQMKTgwhLKPK72E2iGZZPEPoDEeCUp4/sBrSGokHYSdDz6edjumAEx1RsZ/fRtWuWDx8ODFn61wcoNNwpiHrH7m70cAsnkebMANYh+cM7J8B3Bb6rlDFq2ow2ZMEvqRV1570XanMJFxASAppJScbBetIr5DPFfAXzI7q3BcZe3BXzEUSSCQTJEp3tHgRopTzLrk/XN/K3ek0V11TkMjOlFfHQm2FeB995oqUFCjQvaJxtnxNujjWTnD7RtgSjC6RdVisjCd9t6tI0+9AOL40JdgvjAmGBN1MbsA2eLEMwoBMAX0NcBKXgQQ1AHIhubCSgaYBByOnGo5roW9LU/8dmpYSiXqzf8mzZ2wlxpxyJmCHr0J1RchwLfYGOQkCYPpbZ19RW+jk0T+RXwRcFimgjW4Zg4vazgZvUimsXvh+PDlFJUTQrTM/F0JrBPApnMgoMgsaBq+FpDAJztcYcsU/E6NnqoJCKNJlLJ2+r0Ckf/XTbdMa/m5yS7WaJfZDLs71bVg8zsfUdLMQojX8aJ1B6Dvs7V0IGumc/bdmyPT5Y1kG16I5r"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11012","langCode":"en","question":"pt8SW2AnaWFCw9hQJZorGZG0Zm0xOBVNdb3/MSMtcqNq3M7KH87o1DnX9X1F4mlCAbp/Zg8W5r28UXiGO7XOqhgAT4ZVilsmpB2QVZbymr+KKpWACsZTUkTLdvqEygRgfCPp+foziCx7X5fi7Ft4dfKCAz8KApLSZYLnHfpLsxU\u003d","answers":["has slept","sleeps","slept","was sleeping"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"eAjJ9m4GeG2R0U/sPX9t5vDWPC4VTSuv34Nq2HU9gr0B+xOPu5xZqo0cNqGQMXx0Ny5vqWwZS7KBJSDWHRmNQakf7KNxCfqPhJH7Q2W6AVBV1j4SyPigTvdJeqFAsmAURumVqL0oGuGLJQ2Y814Yttw56UaW5QaJsBzWBSGykpbTeAjR75gzR3UKYpOvIzh6atHP+yMhEIvyic5tbKZneEHDPYrmNeSD4OUCFlCaHsJhcrhlyXoAEZXary9TSaQUisRV5iC6GKdnRvFAXAaBTQAy2NrpE/+WNvrogfVccGh6dcYZsCV8AdhbsqEFfnHXuiJ7bj0dXyxnO4bDGdlVwYHImDuX7O1DiVOQ2mfWs+UISyjyu9hNohmWTxD6AxHgpI7NILB6CDG7XLO71qUClJeLyKOEB5tPKNPN5Idr9GA6hWY8fOdwVm2ipBUBRu9g7xn/yDqWFlM//ZmKjpCuPY4XMDH8UwZNojHkIZZa3FudQbtXLESi0pW+IK3r/Pk8MpN4DjJrujGDxXYwjYU9LFK7/VQzOuE/ZwP9AOX0J6Z7QniqJSjaQsO0noU7/4rnDitSQ15fUyF4Zsd/Pbz7w8HrSrhbgJoZbVTAN/AjFbqMpZw564Z4vdpghazBRCsAxJzCpul9z+yuNy620q369zWLXETQgyN7XYbva3zdxMW4xts8Ny2dDrJ15nsw7Esnc4pno7OnmEESydG8nolwhFFArtsGEFheGUGozhjnR+6sGVVYFnIvjUg35kxspnw8c95iXHQf0sSkBxWFITq6h6EZ1/ENvKl8MJjb0wLSMu9HNTCWrducSXrTHpVfHUwiemYcvn4zvnazXAvr4qBUKK/UdbZ0OJzRFY6C3PDzc1yLYrtjt6KZjEtZP7kuRntKRgaXgX5Jt8EIU8wSCs51Rw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11013","langCode":"en","question":"+JzF6mH+hM2tU4GyUKoBN0p1mv1q8sIVhWQgKVyCAhXUio4iPyoORnBRNsFxvUHG","answers":["have practised","were practising","practised","practise"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"fbYUV1ZLKlcp62xprJGr3N/dltg2nd0tQxx1OFtTFIMJTfw9oW7fyMxwu3Uom1aWDMo6Kc3EAz5t1gJNYl0BAv6H79fnd+dn1Yfe/Fw90Cjt8Y85a17YWFsSqwptodmYw215HdGA0O4AHw8Ji7WyP+I+SKh6sxGdF4gPL9paGDEmWSWJWncczauPmSK3UUsOCEso8rvYTaIZlk8Q+gMR4KSOzSCweggxu1yzu9alApSXi8ijhAebTyjTzeSHa/RgOoVmPHzncFZtoqQVAUbvYO8Z/8g6lhZTP/2Zio6Qrj2OFzAx/FMGTaIx5CGWWtxbnUG7VyxEotKVviCt6/z5PDKTeA4ya7oxg8V2MI2FPSxSu/1UMzrhP2cD/QDl9Ceme0J4qiUo2kLDtJ6FO/+K5w4rUkNeX1MheGbHfz28+8PB60q4W4CaGW1UwDfwIxW6jKWcOeuGeL3aYIWswUQrAMScwqbpfc/srjcuttKt+vc1i1xE0IMje12G72t83cTFuMbbPDctnQ6ydeZ7MOxLJ3OKZ6Ozp5hBEsnRvJ6JcIRRQK7bBhBYXhlBqM4Y50furBlVWBZyL41IN+ZMbKZ8PHPeYlx0H9LEpAcVhSE6uoehGdfxDbypfDCY29MC0jLvRzUwlq3bnEl60x6VXx1MInpmHL5+M752s1wL6+KgVCiv1HW2dDic0RWOgtzw83Nci2K7Y7eimYxLWT+5LkZ7Sn9aJf5Vibnj7c8/sKiSfCk\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11014","langCode":"en","question":"ZYknjPCTO9xFupyS7ycdXCjQn1j9ZZkQhBU16bWHEQiD2H1kIHG9FQceqii0UNJ2/Kv/kmM/p65UUVlt4h5RcQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["has worked","worked","works","was working"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"fbYUV1ZLKlcp62xprJGr3AqBAwwC8f/j4KAyDo7TyreclIKp+ZyVSQDW/qDWUI7uLKO/ATYUgxPZNLJav7/UPHu7I+wn1ZXwxeurm9Cj7KsdW9MKLGzzF/obieE085+wv6lM27j+AuEAr9KjTKwAkdZzVjjEIUdeVhDhDsy4nkOtQITmIrfUtkw0Qkh6XTaCIZ1qCG4YWatvIkrAFwu/8whLKPK72E2iGZZPEPoDEeALJmc3zhqSayrBU1pKmOokDitSQ15fUyF4Zsd/Pbz7w4X+FFNJzs8/Mu53kBmLGQiv50VJq2xaFfrs5KrWd6j8VX0d9WwpUbIolCI+jA6p8HSBisK9DjzohDfLFBRp57L3PAlIHWV2TQgtLdqn7ByYKcBM95kHEBEg00nZm27bPdNBbTcKyzye+ocDNV68qykBXDQSKNFkrSLx8SEqUukYvoQbwNVraXWlD0Ahdg9VlEsd82RgOyPTJIK6G31fuxikkNx9Lbi3yebtmBM+bddeO1au1gCtQaMr0Vsf1NynRjWobOMatihzJEA3H58X9WKhjtwA0IhHd+ATTQAKGuEEkVulYkQ9GlgNPeWwRuBdNKvF8q8p0OUK+gU3rYKcK7bPdCQTRYOd1ZVvuaOz07SXMHMDrCdJt3eYeof8I0pBwiqJ/TUh3I45HvtqoQTOvaPPyU760yZz10vPsdtqylGsJgysNozFEnP1S8Qw5ud7TmC4Um3Z5dsoRAFhBgkhlOMDWH7wIP1vG56rQJx2d3XW"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11015","langCode":"en","question":"bTorxbymaQDGk8owHi0xNDKebGJNLl/JIdB6zDaTk8BsXYFPv6P6/+aIc+g/cONz+vRpsWJFhPuGsm8REz2sCHl3vv97GVO2GTTAL1l9TBU\u003d","answers":["signs","are signing","signed","were signing"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"1nNWOMQhR15WEOEOzLieQ7P530SSHreOZwIIe+zR+BGj2e2UArN8RN+VhzoHWIf9UpPiImZml0xEVWibJ/R8zP59DLcfvosSDNn/dpRHb4v/e4OjSGJQqsHCgc8W4sw6HRveD6RKL6Q8kAuupcPgb4E3UxuwDZ4sQzCgEwBfQ1zvAOG65NQWihJD+bMPQP37XaCgyHrlHo/JTz9r8dYY3Iw5W1MaYUOR6zuSm96+XIe5azBnw+zHTu/Lwn+eRpe1CEso8rvYTaIZlk8Q+gMR4BUVToDShqczqIeCUaauF+2Xi8ijhAebTyjTzeSHa/RgOoVmPHzncFZtoqQVAUbvYO8Z/8g6lhZTP/2Zio6Qrj2OFzAx/FMGTaIx5CGWWtxbnUG7VyxEotKVviCt6/z5PDKTeA4ya7oxg8V2MI2FPSxSu/1UMzrhP2cD/QDl9Ceme0J4qiUo2kLDtJ6FO/+K5w4rUkNeX1MheGbHfz28+8PB60q4W4CaGW1UwDfwIxW6jKWcOeuGeL3aYIWswUQrAMScwqbpfc/srjcuttKt+vc1i1xE0IMje12G72t83cTFuMbbPDctnQ6ydeZ7MOxLJ3OKZ6Ozp5hBEsnRvJ6JcIRRQK7bBhBYXhlBqM4Y50furBlVWBZyL41IN+ZMbKZ8PHPeYlx0H9LEpAcVhSE6uoehGdfxDbypfDCY29MC0jLvRzUwlq3bnEl60x6VXx1MInpmHL5+M752s1wL6+KgVCiv1HW2dDic0RWOgtzw83Nci2K7Y7eimYxLWT+5LkZ7So/ViMSiOJxWolgQMKMQtCs\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11016","langCode":"en","question":"H2CdtjGNLrjixqAp2K6/z5zKbXOXvOVhQq9c8MlVUIJZO8x67MH/sqBA5jd91Pe2xWFirY85rtJh2gmyaSYyRQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["aren’t going","weren’t going","were going","are going"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x18120RjqecmJzaB2Xg/9cncDGzltxj2Oj+OL4h+VKJJ6XwRMN5bDE3Mzt5rAXytACCStV/NXRtjgmLAneQfeMyqFNF5wPmauQhHTQMCFwBX2u1WWiWoLmvOgvQ/Afjfuj6EGAGqph0EXHKkVhxX7RTH7HPjXacFTBUuIzDAGBuC/cYr2YMhzKfcc/32deDkwSeHg/s6HyrB/0aqkHhTg5FcU0U3UZmd4wLpssifpM0o7CEso8rvYTaIZlk8Q+gMR4C3tfg3UBI8LgMIjw8UWKzcOK1JDXl9TIXhmx389vPvDhf4UU0nOzz8y7neQGYsZCK/nRUmrbFoV+uzkqtZ3qPxVfR31bClRsiiUIj6MDqnwdIGKwr0OPOiEN8sUFGnnsvc8CUgdZXZNCC0t2qfsHJgpwEz3mQcQESDTSdmbbts900FtNwrLPJ76hwM1XryrKQFcNBIo0WStIvHxISpS6Ri+hBvA1WtpdaUPQCF2D1WUSx3zZGA7I9MkgrobfV+7GKSQ3H0tuLfJ5u2YEz5t1147Vq7WAK1BoyvRWx/U3KdGNahs4xq2KHMkQDcfnxf1YqGO3ADQiEd34BNNAAoa4QSRW6ViRD0aWA095bBG4F00q8XyrynQ5Qr6BTetgpwrts90JBNFg53VlW+5o7PTtJcwcwOsJ0m3d5h6h/wjSkHCKon9NSHcjjke+2qhBM69o8/JTvrTJnPXS8+x22rKUawmDKw2jMUSc/VLxDDm53tOYLhSbdnl2yhEAWEGCSGU40URNdQiVIJZe9Bs3LisG/M\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11017","langCode":"en","question":"DR1wO1f0FXCNJH6E4F7l7nwz8lqZk/TykYJGi7Rir5HAeBkvXLZgPQ4C7QRKqtMS1IqOIj8qDkZwUTbBcb1Bxg\u003d\u003d","answers":["leave","was leaving","leaves","were leaving"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x16BRhz7UHo4fySEzv4mc4ukmQsVFezNAZII2MDqamXGGqNPNNQgPYJmIDYwL8brZkLVw9YcZR67SkOxX6eYjkxvK97J+I5dI3joUXVn95QoIBPaupykbodnj6CK2Gc0Q+jPcP9nc0m2Bp0ephb0Lsd31ADDlk9JWgUktObwMtBLljdW+EeBI8TpLB7pkA9Z5S3RO3x0ynPRCOQHZom6n8E/OpY7e14MymZAIptEIaSz3CEso8rvYTaIZlk8Q+gMR4InbrlIxw6zgaunB2SyBNpfV9MGshOzhJ7H2XLgA2beKUe3VFwmUywSU67uiTU+qo8ONvHljv1kcvvxPuvHiUra+lgs2PVXJnhnDxwRQbmBhPV6ssVKW8RJO66Ok2dNAJ/9wjzToCCUwOEiE+OMG+3mFO21mh5C+qNZeKuG+5TBGIw3K8Kk8b34BJ6e2nkiPs2VW3j0OxCOpfNFz6ve3VL9sfJfClWEbYZJVoWzayEnDhjaJ6qmIr+QN1mDFcpZ+ELUCoI4mIllnGszPiAdpk4KdkoHkx31zMgxbfZKvqVH7sDErZJxpR6WWRkD5h1wI9ykdKOxgJUYPCYQFCiEOF0VJkRrlNM/9ViRURVApBHsU+JrQg7DX1a9j03Z7YeCvItgSMLle04hPBTOnTvXnBlSuTkbZP8V5i+52Z1PbFRwUN3522+NTQgfRAQJxUbyk4VKCYVLRlHNXqf0n1kJIXboP79i6pfwzyIMdJba0uj7EG4crUmtUM+lFUmdr0mmvUdbq7J0JJxYxuSdB+oxIiPQ\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11018","langCode":"en","question":"rZxNcXvpO8trtTOMAmnXY7j0a1nSq3FI7g4qssA9iWtnI6Jh9Ofo6JGh8MHvFo2itMPndt2qwRlHEn/ahAhPQA\u003d\u003d","answers":["was/complaining","have/complained","is/complaining","has/complained"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"fbYUV1ZLKlcp62xprJGr3GNlAgbRaY2HncmTKg3NxneBCxxFMC/UeccazByWlPAgfoXaQgaoby1rTeSQRpz7Cj6fU26KFmw4PH7QRlR9Un/x4xQS6I/tbNuFWmwIMUOGw+nK4W03N1/EQ2H6s5QYhgfkUkcprfNVsWYvHy56wFCRlN/h2Jqmx4Zs327Qa35zoj+Pq4DypVtUmHKkbOJdJN8um5rsOCAs09RPujwyxU/2Q359Nz94JrEtnEf2ED/ymXd/A5AI7JAY6YtHvkGMSQhLKPK72E2iGZZPEPoDEeCOUMYQ633Dr59ww9k8t89ThLGDKbarTlRnZ7TYcnzzj9tvUG2/g51aVl6rJ4Xkupoow+XMi5ozeY9elYlAIxgCS8NVRlaJXbNiU2HyCpLaTmGNmBnayUSYRpJRI4+9ocrDdiN3QCb0pu1V53OaAC6cMfsmWKYKtJUhq99gBR8LvxjVpbNm4ha+VWHIRT7a5vG6YATHVGxn99G1a5YPHw4M4ExYqhaTlEiV2xQ2DGylQ8l+rTQbkOqIeHkglFbBgBKxe4RP1wzdmr7KgdyqFkGvp8ns/S9OBFLQ1Fn6PgOW14kOStbNr8djsnCfX0EXiJs0ZigALIJrBe7YcYIp8TPc8CgXbjdhKWpWgtLo20mGdC7B6AvOvD1MSJm+GzteqzVenYdTzubVkcXyBJHnAgZKlx3YMZdcmaXx9KrMy1OE6kgIpNBdub0lI7XLA3zioFAXas+SH8GZ1/iAEMc4sBaP3y6bmuw4ICzT1E+6PDLFT/ZDfn03P3gmsS2cR/YQP/IIjIpwcFcbjVKtZmXybg9O"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11019","langCode":"en","question":"CbzFjiiTOTBIVcZfWO/VCO83BhpJImC542fPRBRaxH0+SAWlYej9fs2CRuQlo2EYW8DA4YTzH10tfwlZBJPCJg\u003d\u003d","answers":["is/crying","has/cried","was/crying","has/been crying"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"fbYUV1ZLKlcp62xprJGr3OhCkJRgx+X3QnZxeipNRlB+hdpCBqhvLWtN5JBGnPsKPp9TbooWbDg8ftBGVH1Sf/HjFBLoj+1s24VabAgxQ4bD6crhbTc3X8RDYfqzlBiGB+RSRymt81WxZi8fLnrAUD2XEhz2bce+AZB2EOiCXVY+f6sgS2gsuyjEnrHQ2ylrCkGYH0a23QuSy/ggU15Zm+w/z5Bh40WrNf6RfRbQqiwISyjyu9hNohmWTxD6AxHgg/hKLuV6vRLUAafYtuEfAb66zwpbxsJzzqRRl1TI5DLwttiOU/G9Vx2bVfCE4V56GlAC9lWbO+AV59AGPS6WxzhyXHYKwbWLfqWTFLQcdVh6qx05f+u4htjCZG551tAGPUQpWz0aUeZGsy12LVBHSaYKPdZlpLa0ekB4Hsm/u5v3pch9ow/f/0FnJzzKXlu/I9UQnotYz6+NKoIF3TFb99+PkJYCB947dAcPaF92y/LqgMX7JHtFUjkKUPB0XzrZ/J3zPzz2tC3i3OafSo3B6AW5mvnDJGriYHj3qW08fV9h6+/C1Pi3qzkcPD6ml/vD3lfvGqllyKsHSrh+ljSKxCuzZ2xwBCDP6+eesxvCqyr+RdTyWSg+6Zz0O1oFHwAmvz28TGg/NLgmACGDdhc9RifdNFMILKHyNOTb2WyGRAEZmGI75hl1m9oCJQoUXklyfsKoQ0/KqUhrEBKj6HzHgZDCxln8MsFw2qax3nGZQAyGIzrFqdku2i8fhf44sMfIuoJxhBklupitohKN1z4E4g\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11020","langCode":"en","question":"GAMxc65DwHy+gW9hcEQujiFReg/d/BZVyfH/P+a3BXvWIH/SIAEUozsmGoSq6IKXpe7I0Nr/mRsxwxlbhivGBI8YaA4PoLvooTMJbG4dG/tXtE34e+er8mI1Agfi5QDJks1ArX3LmLWf3unzrIEF+A\u003d\u003d","answers":["have played","plays","played","had played"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1/vwnxiA7sLNufjdrmmGtcFp/fiM4PuxBajrRkDRLQUGtlQMNwuwpSbLnCoo0b7Vpm4CNzbUHK/7mIaxzoJUPPSnAi5GD4YGPf30ZQdkkHdhGBjhPRd95OHO/hvlzO/3Ov+tGjWBMHI7IxqALc0sGgM7PhJgLV2czFV/IxYEvZASB4Im7OYkkeKVd+suMnBrzSrxrkRwWGcdg+m6CieWHt1J1kaGILrH9/K7DTjef0MwCyZnN84akmsqwVNaSpjqJJHMFIXOXw51TZPE8ryXMNVZ+tcHKDTcKYh6x+5u9HALY/mh/sRoOOSAplnYh3nZjsCbifq/AFpR1grBed0a+KWZLE/MPSX9Z6ieonQRyD0wOjH4pdGi76NL/wKffmJODKG0jTw2QtSTAOwJ9yzCg7GHggR1SsW5IvDNyg3wNH3qIu5HEkKyJwTVyLBzzIIx/grohqjNlC3Op1ffZ9ygTrMj6ULj3CeM3Bpsv77H8B2jjm/CkUjJLTpwNPpM/wqY24DYEeRbrPSyWa8TmpI9yFyxQy/4VcbN5eadW38b0nO1eOWf/SmDa9MZ0popla8gSJJmBEu1w+cDlY9XeTsmch6TxlrblFbc3hxBsZb0NCbysVAY9DCqUNFcytxvS7JV7u8faxs0/0hjaCSu75XGAplQFgoBYjifXlo9Tt5ln62jPIddeKo1O+dE8V+cYYobmM53N/EZrYvqCYDVTGo7kH6+R6zWdjJc+QzgPjvZYz8AXJDvnxfpXpoWAU5OaxvQYA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11021","langCode":"en","question":"VPi3j0AmMZE/ztTJqxIVCynRleiX6Er13yHS32vU/smlyyY2lmyWZhC/4hU95+qpwkr2+RunQeL0My1uUWZy7Gdhb8H4tMAhjXKfvUN/uXE5J3vunxlBtnzKG5Bl7W2o7JS62TPIFCTFAkUYkGHsxjvI5WZbh5AdDsmoLDoJn592ZFjvae9snXu419rr0O4h","answers":["had sent out","has sent out","sent out","sends out"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1+Ig4YXJmlbZ+0BMu4qXCTX34WWatmI8QuZTEdb7M0TtYhBAvgcANd7D4Mi3bt0X4Qi3HPoar/c+uk0d8OrEW5BuqEeTD4jZyVvsvI1bXHLkkWReKqvf2kiT70xQTLIGLlPRxgJaL7IDxz+bPNLAFRoISyjyu9hNohmWTxD6AxHgdlXzz0CCMVQwrltfVlEMuYHVxIsju4ry+HIa9PEkhwvbb1Btv4OdWlZeqyeF5LqacMVWSLVbJs8QXo6y9M5Tafc9janRNXObXq2iR9a0MXWuBihdCmQMFUmnOe03P3Hd1IMwB8WeuRugWWJulkj+yhJXUKCIy96doXuPxRy35yw3LvPbqe/+XL80HkO/858wTXCdsZE0k1cBZLDvgsGzTIGW8yw9FVFenNwkiFReigAssdTa3vY1/77e6H0n9ZugEBAE+tZH7jdCcL8aXQBOk3WUYtYJHxqti4C04PtKqkMqQb1IQTxbBhxm95DiiCu2sD73ye7XObgUrnEs080p0LFUpmaD25UA85vq2AwMyvQLRsY7T8rGFF3GgTMSqFUohLPPUUG1Afqz1fbQ3+wW7JACPgnCfxGmuXdAqDgz2MbfkncImJcNDJijaCxm5MOdpabePzISzu6W6qS/nbCuTIuqxrSF/9lwNCW25hC52j7dL0K+eP6QUAnjHJvfKcAdhhOB7sAuyrGwfH541BwecQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11022","langCode":"en","question":"hq12uRnJ7M7vrQfOuynSuMghhiNI0Lm3YvaNsvX2b2vOJO7uOMRw/sZHDe8q9KlqmwHVZQkfTBBlcwlAK+KdmUBEUnZYStzEykNMStU8Bk7fhpask+wJQqDETk207MVg46xti0QWxleWZn+LeX5g0w\u003d\u003d","answers":["volunteered","has volunteered","volunteers","had volunteered"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"z+qO0n/orfgIUb19/N5lHRoK3Pz86PsIllEmBWH3uHWBXBHLlz2CeCeyxgW9wk6bYYDIVP3DmKYKaPb9XphxSIGW8yw9FVFenNwkiFReigAssdTa3vY1/77e6H0n9Zug2lu2YjsdNzbmdNcubYLI2Hs7dp8d42CtgdKBnykghN7eJFsUSSep73mw0tYy1BUALu7MxKXG9lHPZe/hY+GUQghLKPK72E2iGZZPEPoDEeBL9nE8pn0aZHmVrD9g8jeGhf4UU0nOzz8y7neQGYsZCOiyecchEZTJv+uGIqTv3gNxxuIXirOGVn1AHB5/sj3PRSgVsgofyiBZaR4Qg2TcxuPlD8kXIDCpJthR9mMaQjcNfIWD0JcaDZRMOWR2WFDj8LFlXWOhV2O/1xW5Y1ra2SKk95R1AgQ7KVl58ge2Y8wdJABWEm0f+L108yEzkM3wWFFZsdqlq+7WgiHce1X7CUpbCHscchEKo0OdMr2hH3V70PBO1C2JbzuKriZTuBUfDSpm3rDkiZT9ilns7BlTIqnJ802rr2kJUfx6inpFaLx/8EcZTWDWzfTY1vP9gzIwqWt24OGY+lTkavGcigli0bHkaNOIRuD8mNrW7GhB1TCgJwNni+1yUhzsQsnfA0qbGd/32ggz+sUzAz9LfMh2yJ4Z2MEJ4p4fDnoxPTCewAVK3UQw6yz1yHT3SkyIXrhV0qtLRJG3SGsmVvxb410QVd/H7219G70Am6fV8xO8CKY\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11023","langCode":"en","question":"pt8SW2AnaWFCw9hQJZorGUSR8cr31DuPCVHQb0RnPsZ6m1lXIw9N0MM6T7w7mmnC/wF9iNHC1gyw+8NwrARafadBZpWoaOa0T3g0yirw9QhUFr2GmpIEO2fw6IrVE22/TQ2oBcMjyrSrksqb6u0rWw\u003d\u003d","answers":["had slept","has slept","sleeps","slept"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1yA0JS48tJ76CBfyTdsur0s5lm6BHt0ck4HbJnGfYKc0WfFMNbRPZTx/daUv1fBduFqXzN/WUmD74jiumSpoAtv7Pi4j6/E6SKcBq3jUxcZMN3TTXnAlzhVoYhkzqaOZVzuh9eG6Au6tp41wsPVUlvMISyjyu9hNohmWTxD6AxHg32TDLaVXAz2T0XbPjJENMsZOsge7XWP84nbKQNpGlBPl9lEYL8Cu07pMb9KV/Chba6zqQVCdVBDt5L7riexW3T8zvWTdg0nXsboO8zwAb5THrYz/GVBlqNytcDZLwes0AS+JsiThk6UIVSNpCb/K0H+BcPVyOXL6q0scYpm/RrqlgAAyZj49dE1e24Ad68Y5aWNYIxF0wGbQOnX0R9LS0sPu3H6YjHzIESIP7egPhrnEW4YZ6G/EHuo0VYvfsos8wrNq/dU0Lr59rE/r+tOmY+kCKgjJBXXjZbPVTTDKYZMFQm5pBuY3RbR916S5gM/PEqVraa3VK2su7RE6dmhj/frQ4i/VrEHaUMMnEVnxX73wEDFsIAhkGo5gIw8TvGyohbpgQORDZsEpw9/HtWuQxK6/Ud2XGXbNTxpXFMK+sLCzG4QYbSnYewYxOSoBNYM7g5d03jCylvlyJybPkWVeQpu80f3s7ytMUJvMMyYi/eQ0gJpbukScKS7dYnKxQ1HGhG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11024","langCode":"en","question":"L/JIGndwKfFVwC8XjPqDNegVlGdNRm5SdXn3/UFI/gGtHfK20F8E+xFvFe0GpFpnGkju+N7Y+ninygTsTmTpgo2oYiWZKEHefe7TNx5mroCX/S8HW7NejZVxY0H0n/Lhf9CQdPeLStKDAWW5LC/Dlw\u003d\u003d","answers":["plays","have played","had played","played"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1/vwnxiA7sLNufjdrmmGtcE4pe0z+il+3CrSarlTzzqZWFFZsdqlq+7WgiHce1X7CUpbCHscchEKo0OdMr2hH3WapJcTi8VB64mB7pq0p9UtF5g2KubpJKQWvLmsJtSOrheN7Rp76IjiDnrEeInSAvUISyjyu9hNohmWTxD6AxHgDxnEUKRXJW4NJJKCyUaVi5zysVpKl2i3+RhqnY7H/OzsrFsqbOnEJbSgP/L6A5vim8//up3/OiXPkKHGRe3ks+mKu7wdnPEN77lAbEKBnZPot4fb4/1xnA6XMDCcaZAEqVmmuNiNmG4zhR9gHRDl1OCIbY9cntWH+zB1qbmCYRb0lDdimZTV+jK6S1P5S9pyHohB7eHBJfrWzEydvERO6uQXwUKdhgcROZUtHMP96VFv4JBAZ4Qva3Ms2RP+nLSVnPEp6z64fJ+gedeVYEdOihtFVCAVCVdQOkXQD27L0TlvuqnKhUfEwfm8k5Q8mEtLUYNc9UoWuUlt01CoCXn+1IQ9hd7VKq3H6VyPv1XQh/GMhdxLWBb0yOXxF34gbT/nwFN0wU86ayM802MLyrAF/Rd+GRip5BzpsnijCFmck8jyGI+Ts+Id75aP2mJlsuwBG+xLky6CldCBWcr43ZJ8Vr2z+mHJkRLsRPMGvmUCGVqRKfENgdQ8uFnLeBQBx3jttVUODdij2ujqueBKZTpfGQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11025","langCode":"en","question":"F6BOpbDMvadWFOhteYEjVE7Ds5A3IXf+xHf2kP+osilk3SnkxipBImpDeL9giFkJjEALwPpj0JwWejhqlf7Hwg\u003d\u003d","answers":["have worked","had worked","worked","has worked"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x17v699XD2JN3s4EQwqpYlWDC7q4wla1Xi2BlXX+KAYHSDSpm3rDkiZT9ilns7BlTIrCHkFeh8JLG+E5cK6mEGzAgc5/NbnFPo8MQUGMvu/hx+k03EOeHusPcA3To75XC59QrUw2jSjKGh+Fm2JHOE6xOZx86ek/W7H03y7gFh4SQPiABe4dWmPv5aF0794wYrNwz3Xhc0un+OdINSwlDGNF/gXD1cjly+qtLHGKZv0a68LbYjlPxvVcdm1XwhOFeeoTae/l/36jEhA1STb/CtJs6pMsKyMnuxtUxfiGENEd+TLQOn7QTngAw5147EvOpp+F6BgEPk7zpHzTasg+YZ+DDtH3G9kgI10bessdm9vwKU/+/L0uSTKj1rzKEKkF8Brt15EKyXxF3Cz6JAUvoyQ/wIG8MMjrIx4j4fo1fKRT+WfFMNbRPZTx/daUv1fBduFqXzN/WUmD74jiumSpoAtvnKOQbJdfqtpYScMBCGUY3gTdTG7ANnixDMKATAF9DXLkvUs4MtNG7kTcLBR5lol1XCx5Ghah50fYSgLQyYmAefnsxEI4xUCTpC4odyqcBOTdJLRVUBwVwAkzTToDWBQ33yqg2xgpVhDmaJ2YhOfwFPMFzofSFPjFQwjFO/yBjMA+OMFsvkWkbdlJDgMCXOxvRr7iOQuEYtoCP7H0NxTqihEhKPBpXaOUitUAc/bhqAdgCZGqtaoUPFzgjJNWvPD8\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11026","langCode":"en","question":"PvJ3qAVJfJjwDRKLIHaVO/JMXHbXy3tjECBj722KrfLzsErB+qiOpHiHg/j/3Xf+ktUk/07x2cEYeArITe/wxw\u003d\u003d","answers":["have turned","had turned","turned","turns"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"fbYUV1ZLKlcp62xprJGr3IAbgt/Q7uiyMtRbWaiV4892RnRrHCvbFWmyv5hW8PgR6VcPpG1CaEWiWD+hw1IEiSyZ75KGXzr6hc7GyaFrQGrtU2w//YxZbBvGWT/h2ZLkfKmhgYng4aWxFCloYhL78wfkUkcprfNVsWYvHy56wFBhMltLcD8MStkkLFQp1KcxPn+rIEtoLLsoxJ6x0Nspaw0qZt6w5ImU/YpZ7OwZUyKpyfNNq69pCVH8eop6RWi8f/BHGU1g1s302Nbz/YMyMOK1G5LjCnHus2WtV5BOou0ISyjyu9hNohmWTxD6AxHgdlXzz0CCMVQwrltfVlEMuYHVxIsju4ry+HIa9PEkhwvbb1Btv4OdWlZeqyeF5LqacMVWSLVbJs8QXo6y9M5Tafc9janRNXObXq2iR9a0MXWuBihdCmQMFUmnOe03P3Hd1IMwB8WeuRugWWJulkj+yhJXUKCIy96doXuPxRy35yw3LvPbqe/+XL80HkO/858wTXCdsZE0k1cBZLDvgsGzTIGW8yw9FVFenNwkiFReigAssdTa3vY1/77e6H0n9ZugEBAE+tZH7jdCcL8aXQBOk3WUYtYJHxqti4C04PtKqkMqQb1IQTxbBhxm95DiiCu2sD73ye7XObgUrnEs080p0LFUpmaD25UA85vq2AwMyvQLRsY7T8rGFF3GgTMSqFUohLPPUUG1Afqz1fbQ3+wW7JACPgnCfxGmuXdAqDgz2MbfkncImJcNDJijaCxm5MOdpabePzISzu6W6qS/nbCuTIuqxrSF/9lwNCW25hC52j7dL0K+eP6QUAnjHJvfKcAdDbw7dRgReeNIPAMKbQxr0Q\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11027","langCode":"en","question":"YldHCA8rc+xi2ZIfIpDVuJB0Zv7G3If3ttj582lqtwnMHRuSv8aLdzenlTjLgt1DTiiAAdYhoXeEuH8gBDxqAw\u003d\u003d","answers":["have been","was","had been","am"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x13YDPIfu7moMS59ZQ3jSfo9TLY4yaWciw4UeqCB/GLUqM9oqWOOn/HiXFPGIu1Cc9TMNofZYc+y+SlMRD94IEJPfG6uAkMKhTpCZUHBqXbLyr31DLkdUPE2RTYUs5I92RUM/D7u4uywDfHHsomjFYv/LXy1wzpinqySd54sSiZj2CEso8rvYTaIZlk8Q+gMR4Ev2cTymfRpkeZWsP2DyN4aF/hRTSc7PPzLud5AZixkI6LJ5xyERlMm/64YipO/eA3HG4heKs4ZWfUAcHn+yPc9FKBWyCh/KIFlpHhCDZNzG4+UPyRcgMKkm2FH2YxpCNw18hYPQlxoNlEw5ZHZYUOPwsWVdY6FXY7/XFbljWtrZIqT3lHUCBDspWXnyB7ZjzB0kAFYSbR/4vXTzITOQzfBYUVmx2qWr7taCIdx7VfsJSlsIexxyEQqjQ50yvaEfdXvQ8E7ULYlvO4quJlO4FR8NKmbesOSJlP2KWezsGVMiqcnzTauvaQlR/HqKekVovH/wRxlNYNbN9NjW8/2DMjCpa3bg4Zj6VORq8ZyKCWLRseRo04hG4PyY2tbsaEHVMKAnA2eL7XJSHOxCyd8DSpsZ3/faCDP6xTMDP0t8yHbInhnYwQninh8OejE9MJ7ABUrdRDDrLPXIdPdKTIheuFXSq0tEkbdIayZW/FvjXRBV1pyjvBMqxuWa1WReh2kNBw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11028","langCode":"en","question":"I2AOg9GU3jmU+Y43VS9zIVLlqenW4KhC1ZSIQSqD1d276nFrv+q4TKqx8W+LELKY4XpdycnQ4pbEnS7q2f6v7g\u003d\u003d","answers":["is","was","has been","had been"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x13YDPIfu7moMS59ZQ3jSfo82G+8ctZuXODDe4ipbzB88y+BLuR9OjN+08kjOThsXsCjUnnkfSmu6Vx3Ym7ebwd7LOqLTg1Qqu60Ejgmcj68X5BfBQp2GBxE5lS0cw/3pUW/gkEBnhC9rcyzZE/6ctJVmYqHSDOYH2s1eNcFkAeFxzmwC4gyWBzxaonWMdr8luOCuz5zt4NLj72chWgqO5EIz4SeVJ9B94E3L2ro24ZmCASAhcGstai2nFxnfiDhfqU2eNd/z5MkByhmuYGhY4g2z81n2DLhEINZnDtNibg9IUR1mec3oA43/+HhvqkA0O98Aa7vXgXyF3RBk+l23YWnLw7BYv8ld3ErXyu2eJjwaXR98ZyJMnFUgfJh48yuDJSxmswatvJKXzz/XgV6o9pjp9QAJDpy8zbxij935DXAwJgysNozFEnP1S8Qw5ud7Tjuw2ntJdEE32oeh6mEpE6DMOPOwRhE6B4p37JqgsQ0xP8Ct1fDflPevp8036K068K2wP/N8JGdesg7mchTiFnMKb7sYFOV+xdpJPkCD5UwV5bleOoN3Pfr0UGFhqTSeFWwoYujCgbXp85JVPhpOKGKzhPPZg6deCH+prYx+M34M9DX0VMoFLlebWQ83c3CH8gndzTNcdJIYZMJ3pWa2D9jTr83OzoVc6+/kzzjmKNrx98PWRWxc59S+ILOQCJu4Pl2/UiX7UyXvYJ2NP38kIXF7nodKm16jrGxpSxzO2uBiyGwTfNNQ9IyoIlpSEui2zg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11029","langCode":"en","question":"RSavSGllzkNN7hLtq371deNW6qB0udyoAuWTMQ95wpU8rWvgVYiCy4g6+HJjkOlc","answers":["have never been","was not","had never been","has never been"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"fbYUV1ZLKlcp62xprJGr3PdavL/x+SQeFVr2FwORUnSY5tCpD80ALhq71wYQXkux4sb1SHqb9qs659+9iKqq6N0SttxQWt0Il32P1raZLP307IQNVz4bWmn6JD6URg3ZfUFyqtQzzGKLpK6XjHo72lV47FuLkkNM7636mxjbaUaT1y67Q6hs1IQnhkoBeD9sHS+IreoPuuubZQqp+DA6YQpvuxgU5X7F2kk+QIPlTBXluV46g3c9+vRQYWGpNJ4VbChi6MKBtenzklU+Gk4oYpnF/WLEeix0ex0N26nzxl0ISyjyu9hNohmWTxD6AxHgjzUlMEZ7rdv7TDwlkon3b+hKCfl5UJNWMG0Td3HSCVIeLoRTv8Ysurr5tq8Bel4G/ncCWRbI1Qmk0CX2uGn5U1rk9+1qfWLgUjN1EmsCKUOEFgW9KRCgUez7MDKOLLUSKZytFIWHoRIoGnhpZpM5KWsrsb6LSle1gjDzoUvujO0enWQpOeiLogY/qv37C8JM6QIqCMkFdeNls9VNMMphk2IQQL4HADXew+DIt27dF+EItxz6Gq/3PrpNHfDqxFuQB7vFrEAw/BxnCOsJHW5bO5wcrmrHOkrrlfNYP99+vqTp6iogQ3gChPuBjdiF/Xyl3GlARGDWQTZHUHRBZPw0buGT6lxcKorUI55LaUykV8FGs8O0ZdZt5Bx6c1nKDwx+GLb2HyjZjbbFT11R/X+D8/FyRjBy6OgaiXDP2pr3Ow+dWWeHI8vY21FV+0keym4docDn/ZAg+ZjUK8xsJw02BH2jCgaX7FCB6fQLvQ60LPn8Qnv0HAI8fvwu1uC7jFXz"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11030","langCode":"en","question":"GqRTmkP/5sN4mlleHSkoA1SF9+oATlHfMnHPzvwzCkWf52pS42nU7TS6Gjkf17vQgN5hws1Ya8WIT0MBbvnm/w\u003d\u003d","answers":["had gone","goes","went","has gone"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"haymPDckd+aWWvS4OcPuBc6AJxlmN5cNKdFIZKFQ+qaBXBHLlz2CeCeyxgW9wk6bTXCdsZE0k1cBZLDvgsGzTIGW8yw9FVFenNwkiFReigAssdTa3vY1/77e6H0n9ZughC3C3KTYGP8Es2l5bnm77g7ZVLMyNluftIjSBWLwkgWE8TC2Z5uptY2kLqe6BdQwCjJrDCaVRfqiVOOdSt23LeVmtHzhO1yaMUWoWLzh12Lrs4uNT4baqV2gk3h6gXOqU3+m5WYoy4570VmDJpeLEmwQG03bgH7uEMhQQNkxORSAkwaSmhAzKPjd4CQal5Ond828sfMLomtWhX1tHOH9C9xvProqQL4dqk70M2XPByAq52Winuosw1BWIPj1+zbMjjWTnD7RtgSjC6RdVisjCeRf2rJj/MhhIub6Y9mnFDccWlbVuHbhqELMZMrq/MZA49IGy4O80blgR5M6vwi6dD/LPjCLqiCGv84dS2OJZMUeiEHt4cEl+tbMTJ28RE7qS+zE33i9Zp3jF+4GIhcuDAFo57eSDWHYulON7w7kJTP8bqQiqT1sJlbj+axwGnfjx59W6z9VxnZNcztP9z3QwslI3NzuVzQEihdYFdxF+BnoAHboCh+4xDDRL+TxA0wKa4qXUMwZwaTt9xmK8XG4dXERvFeKl1m3B+5pQApzpAgYDxnqz0y3kHGewl/rw7ol/D8APutdNOTMfiYqioIqCSiukeTOK6vzNTj2JziOpgE\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11031","langCode":"en","question":"QqC9/XmvaQ0gAwXLEHxwdiGNYOiJR4vsjmwFGQmUaobgBeTFbPNuCwj+tuU70MbYmbbpxSVU9LhYfQ9Gb1GG+AA1HXXNprpR48tx6eTl4JNzPfcLyuxLeyG97dOcAuSMVnYeNAmu3tiNrTL98O3EIw\u003d\u003d","answers":["have had","had","had had","have"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"haymPDckd+aWWvS4OcPuBc6AJxlmN5cNKdFIZKFQ+qY6/wCUfO87JCAwIN+I6pfUoSxl5oTmjG8ROFBxvhrVGe2vFiFXE/heoCtKwVao8u4cKpZ5wUnKUUGb89P8GGC2R/LI8Z2XFGWQhjJSGNH7a7GEjy7bmytXbmCXqs7LoAPMCwZKm2FZ+nIll5moyXt8kx5Alq2gAlaXzjNCPxk+IvWxGyRNdlmj4L1goNIRSNFCwC1G/usmXuAGn1GYxc8bJXnnCsUex1oY/1YzZih4YRIj5j0wQSmtu47q0ezVYiX73dKOJFPJ4zcRYoR+ue541K94S8mxVMes2sn2Z4US3SA8BxieoitZOu7+N4UZTx19U19uzk7a7hnYz+6Ww7qI/KrEYLlueiu2oSwUT3+Nf9xEnjqhARPdSFKziwbBQ3WsmVno7m+nhWWj6Dj//xhJPoCDUYNaeLcPfaig/0i0UUrgN2CVhlDv41A9bf7lq8dNtU+Sxhi+LMfw0RbF8pf1Hxcb3YJFrhpMQUQcSdWDUlyutw6skkJ5Q0EH4nU1omauQZzfCH5LVGPwcpgbbe5u3aKaySOLXlm2Rilrj1x0Xax/rL/E3iEUhkRnXn8HtAuX7Ch8daqHNpAf0M9L8MU/ha60rLQOQiHKU5/Z6DFCUxNBLvvvb+sOoBM3R5jTTEbqlOc33AKVUJlUaMtKWNDpCD4RMpOuzgBSdhQNZ9XyrQT+b7IeOx8/mHhqmHt15Yi2zW0aABpILI9g/D2DrNOiGm+Ig5Wya0lbWYZZ6+y92DjVbovPgt5dUSi4tiC9zgxdjyvlBoJnjY1mOHKF1QxPzZqPZ+bthbR670AeD5p6rP7KhHdUWWVhhCi6ott0pftjSq2+ECFzn3+zl5X/19cgSmghn0UFmZ3QaSeCMBa+Q/gWDu4Tv6AK8HTl/KXxG7OtkzZBeDXpBpjwFgrn3KclU4Ggo3DCoMG3ug3kBixn79VJGrqnx7sNLNnkPZoI2NLX3fncUSzPbUK9JenRzgdZ89yCwQV1i3nd/tnc6ZDDwGzBBw6S1K1TrGv295H3AqghuRecEfEtOhSRVE0M8Cs5M4s3gyCbZRb2KGyipDJRcEvb2xqLCOZ9XkJnxjNaDBJplXO4gPlwkxGyY16Cl05E0a144sgaH4+gOgfD5o7EGKEl36MGB7l+Om9M+eN8ctU\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11032","langCode":"en","question":"0zJUN03438hD+1uM8u5XXpm2NGbR47Xy2XcX85VGHZ5WzM/kKc7BMZvnESljrCWBBln/YZVbyxbigDrQ7Lh44A\u003d\u003d","answers":["sleeps","was sleeping","have slept","slept"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"6stOUyyOtDX54FyK6i6CliBSqbMXD368mbXl1mHXREjqzGvpmLZR7aXLzwlLDLDiqg9rz8awuWCHaFvoaW8maIE3UxuwDZ4sQzCgEwBfQ1wEpeBBDUAciG5sJKBpgEHI6cajmuhb0tT/x2alhKJerN/ybNnbCXGnHImYIevQnVFyHAt9gY5CQJg+ltnX1Fb6vH8fN6ggAx9gDz8M/WOIuA7ZVLMyNluftIjSBWLwkgUY3t25s6CbHFFt5pFHr/RZ1d310WPxnEeOb5PK0AcyqAhLKPK72E2iGZZPEPoDEeDX+ktL/UQGcIMroB8sVnmxA4X7CGMOAGT6bGqchesAC5nm8qm23HhpH/8WhLNfc7/SlHj2CMHF49Hm37hFMLs3V8OJB1MKULnexCZpZ83pLZye9TPmCLPiqZMf5ushV2RcrJ7bln4AD0ZocHDEww4tI2fdk/SRY4f9rOisYetfVCnNBy9uVd3Thwr4iIIeXLw2BamUqnZYrbXqpa8LoIYI0KXtKhz5gYXBQZSANoRibeopqSfuXQiiHPkAXzK167Oo+n6caJR7fxodVseBiK/euDif1+hrykyDB0Bg5VF6UAp/TUY7oa8+hiV/CaAo+tx9ojD/+GIJif8E5MB6RCmXFA3PwQQQafS/pPHE/RcSfqLplRguNk1MHQe1wxsbzCXm8vrhKVnmiHF814c9cneXIU+EH084E7QQSz4yERwlsDj0+UqsRC/MV3+hmaSgmUjSOOEImp9dn9nURXrx/yRhyyITt/mc5UMWtU1vN6AvSNuR09ctaJD46vLrkVoyU6KEbzIZIy8f/vBQNmIt/pHh"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11033","langCode":"en","question":"TaS/Et+cz1pIFaFVBtGDegezLrA6OKkVUq8CfX58t6W+hxeg+2w6Bu67O+g9XI+dcnU+3vE5lNFjVGYr1t0tHqcupxQdEPkFar2Wde+M+Ly7Ca8ydybJ6iFxuU7o3YXlhG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["have turned","had turned","turned","turns"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"6stOUyyOtDX54FyK6i6CliBSqbMXD368mbXl1mHXREjqzGvpmLZR7aXLzwlLDLDiqg9rz8awuWCHaFvoaW8maIE3UxuwDZ4sQzCgEwBfQ1wEpeBBDUAciG5sJKBpgEHI6cajmuhb0tT/x2alhKJerN/ybNnbCXGnHImYIevQnVFyHAt9gY5CQJg+ltnX1Fb6vH8fN6ggAx9gDz8M/WOIuA7ZVLMyNluftIjSBWLwkgWG9j+mYRJRz6Et5apBA7D2CEso8rvYTaIZlk8Q+gMR4CV55wrFHsdaGP9WM2YoeGESI+Y9MEEprbuO6tHs1WIl+93SjiRTyeM3EWKEfrnueNSveEvJsVTHrNrJ9meFEt0gPAcYnqIrWTru/jeFGU8dfVNfbs5O2u4Z2M/ulsO6iPyqxGC5bnortqEsFE9/jX/cRJ46oQET3UhSs4sGwUN1rJlZ6O5vp4Vlo+g4//8YST6Ag1GDWni3D32ooP9ItFFK4DdglYZQ7+NQPW3+5avHTbVPksYYvizH8NEWxfKX9R8XG92CRa4aTEFEHEnVg1JcrrcOrJJCeUNBB+J1NaJmrkGc3wh+S1Rj8HKYG23ubt2imskji15ZtkYpa49cdF2sf6y/xN4hFIZEZ15/B7QLl+wofHWqhzaQH9DPS/DFP4WutKy0DkIhylOf2egxQlMTQS7772/rDqATN0eY00xG6pTnN9wClVCZVGjLSljQ6Qg+ETKTrs4AUnYUDWfV8q0E/m+yHjsfP5h4aph7deWIts1tGgAaSCyPYPw9g6zTohpviIOVsmtJW1mGWevsvdg41W6Lz4LeXVEouLYgvc4MXY8r5QaCZ42NZjhyhdUMT82aj2fm7YW0eu9AHg+aeqz+yoR3VFllYYQouqLbdKX7Y0qtvhAhc59/s5eV/9fXIEpoIZ9FBZmd0GkngjAWvkP4Fg7uE7+gCvB05fyl8RuzrZM2QXg16QaY8BYK59ynJVOBoKNwwqDBt7oN5AYsZ+/VSRq6p8e7DSzZ5D2aCNjS19353FEsz21CvSXp0c4HWfPcgsEFdYt53f7Z3OmQw8BswQcOktStU6xr9veR9wKoIbkXnBHxLToUkVRNDPArOTOLN4Mgm2UW9ihsoqQyUXBL29saiwjmfV5CZ8YzWgwSaZVzuID5cJMRsmNegpdORNGteOLIGh+PoDoHw+aOxBihJd+jBge5fjpvTPnjfHLV"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11034","langCode":"en","question":"u9k5TLE2uGM8yUdeMIBabKdiSUCM/huMcmE5Z5sdZJ/CrDjM2vPsAVH1p5eDtbG3xQGv/G2OqGId4xu/InmEvQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["had gone","went","go","has gone"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"haymPDckd+aWWvS4OcPuBc6AJxlmN5cNKdFIZKFQ+qZLExT2HFRsJ0RzCjiXniGHhjaJ6qmIr+QN1mDFcpZ+ELUCoI4mIllnGszPiAdpk4KdkoHkx31zMgxbfZKvqVH7sDErZJxpR6WWRkD5h1wI9ykdKOxgJUYPCYQFCiEOF0VJkRrlNM/9ViRURVApBHsU/sYEsDqfmm4SVBItEZeTrDeZIsw5xrJITsNXDfUQ43xS7CJsubJNhCMtW7X6cKmfCEso8rvYTaIZlk8Q+gMR4CXMCWg7eN0/kFoCYJDetQKDIP9yTAFgtnEcfHJ95NPLjCtG0j1FCHI6nPrcvCPo5lcVhhgUm63cAcaK57PX9RnNP/TjSGHpyiIrSTfdOnYutHsZLCiQMOutWC1f8tVe6L59YnZkUIYR2AYsMLNv+MWLOavnpJUaJnvuoaISLlwhgDXNfC6CxJB4cPrPAtegaBH1FIDuVqFKQGegX4X/Hz7rJJNayY5oIE4fvZ9fwr2iSoD05qoaxVFU5mJc4iCjZycu7icjRMswizBNze8elWHBlEan6FY17OH1gdU99ljJ/o54G2WPM/WnCKDwyASK4QzPo1k1mHu2OKZ89muZPwMsBrbsngccbmLm1GzL6NS6JgysNozFEnP1S8Qw5ud7Thvbo6yvDOO4qZ1iJzhJW3Cw7QspGNTjafTB/JWUweFv3eT9KVxaYkuP4O+m4U/TAXKjfrHSY4lspupeg/EeW4kO1om76iElsFT6bykppgC4Zst/b2sAWD1huqUZzEV59yl1/UvnVSafub5z98lJ0VkKwwyd84nSUeNMejIXZB69jNbdU9wG7I/B7/h5ZScXc8vVZmxghVFfkYfa7IdGMLME4rxClVkzOFqcv64klicFdf8zRlF97i4GgntGACo90A3AVV2Gn2DAwnKKXME2Iq5I3JVXOdlxZPinrInoN6iCfnrBuhD6v7mgeqqLpD0A2qYE2AsRld6Cue/P4C9X8Ai2FQpVimxxHVeB7OOp+agxUNK6/xwBkii8TYkyIzvgZPGSo18RiRQi3ZD1ayb4M1YhLb3xrvoTyw20w4Pf1xuRnkC+RxPdJeJhfEKn14ClXhU7j+zHrfOKZRvifLupo5AMWJH7Y+QfdtV+rajl44VKvJFplEvO/ZpUBwFsJb2HZYa+c0oHDsQo4yBcFyJIHaA\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11035","langCode":"en","question":"BG0YsiqTwLL8gMLZlHxE7qQ/IsXEpEgf4qGF3OKZ5Rbnh+18umuhpnM8bFeKtkmThG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["had washed","washed","was washing","have washed"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"6stOUyyOtDX54FyK6i6CliBSqbMXD368mbXl1mHXREjqzGvpmLZR7aXLzwlLDLDiqg9rz8awuWCHaFvoaW8maIE3UxuwDZ4sQzCgEwBfQ1wEpeBBDUAciG5sJKBpgEHI6cajmuhb0tT/x2alhKJerN/ybNnbCXGnHImYIevQnVFyHAt9gY5CQJg+ltnX1Fb6vH8fN6ggAx9gDz8M/WOIuA7ZVLMyNluftIjSBWLwkgWgPsPde7rxUPQ2pWnIkxWW6VZITV7jI7mYhwoP6CVE+QhLKPK72E2iGZZPEPoDEeBscggRp8Mr4XvUQJOCaQLomF3zvu7iUGqwcs30j447nuysWyps6cQltKA/8voDm+Kt3u91lavtfjquN3DQAypS+X/CdrQzvFNk7hvBc0g5tb4qQc/0TuYnAOJJ0z/fVkJoB0IOo/H6vYTrfaRUGxefkwWLUevf6NFMfIDuNe4Nxy79/u1qSuYxi/JkIdUqpZIindOMcTZn67WNOoPya/fr+co9+4a3gc+tz5rWF5T7so85Bulm2B5AWSG0+rVaBSHAUlWEZ5wvta02gkj3TXEE+fh/I2HDw/WEl6huXj6DbdmKm1J2mGM4LbyL3aBrPiiI5vNGdn/FhEpauz8eSTB/P6CvR1w71warPNb7EfpMdKlNIaMbfOHM7vnIsP+pHM6FISb3fE2SLoXxT4bv9CpWo95A4Yoyf7RlG5lqAzVBgBwx9NP/UtvziLYSIlH91c3/8phEA+kFgKpA6ceLTX98lQe+eL9aIttKFWMsbNUkAHVQ/bXxGF/f9/B5ddXSPCO1VQ4N2KPa6Oq54EplOl8Z"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11036","langCode":"en","question":"Hky7zoyx0maNZGMT+05eZjXX4DZwuCllCaVyVHWHwZ2CZjRkJOwfUEi6sY5orEr4zIJ968irj3NTvrlAF0NYAZTY8dH2SHUIhra0O+xTJj0\u003d","answers":["have just arrived","has just arrived","just arrived","had just arrived"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"haymPDckd+aWWvS4OcPuBc6AJxlmN5cNKdFIZKFQ+qaBXBHLlz2CeCeyxgW9wk6bTXCdsZE0k1cBZLDvgsGzTIGW8yw9FVFenNwkiFReigAssdTa3vY1/77e6H0n9ZughC3C3KTYGP8Es2l5bnm77g7ZVLMyNluftIjSBWLwkgXZfZafqxgL3Ep61CqMRd3vTQMOlsKzEKJEe8jb8AIJVghLKPK72E2iGZZPEPoDEeDmn7Dv5qqAQlZIftOZWXHB6EoJ+XlQk1YwbRN3cdIJUh4uhFO/xiy6uvm2rwF6Xgb+dwJZFsjVCaTQJfa4aflTWuT37Wp9YuBSM3USawIpQ4QWBb0pEKBR7PswMo4stRIpnK0UhYehEigaeGlmkzkpayuxvotKV7WCMPOhS+6M7R6dZCk56IuiBj+q/fsLwkzpAioIyQV142Wz1U0wymGTYhBAvgcANd7D4Mi3bt0X4Qi3HPoar/c+uk0d8OrEW5AHu8WsQDD8HGcI6wkdbls7nByuasc6SuuV81g/336+pOnqKiBDeAKE+4GN2IX9fKXcaUBEYNZBNkdQdEFk/DRu4ZPqXFwqitQjnktpTKRXwUazw7Rl1m3kHHpzWcoPDH4YtvYfKNmNtsVPXVH9f4Pz8XJGMHLo6BqJcM/amvc7D51ZZ4cjy9jbUVX7SR7Kbh2hwOf9kCD5mNQrzGwnDTYEfaMKBpfsUIHp9Au9DrQs+a2w2nQVBSEGdmrLAos7doM\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11037","langCode":"en","question":"gpfUqEQQGyteExbs8uqgU6As2wUNC6ODbmo09biWX1ttuYDROVqQ9XIALh3r/hQuRA64mTgZaUt1gxcyF418EA\u003d\u003d","answers":["get up","got up","have got up","had got up"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"haymPDckd+aWWvS4OcPuBc6AJxlmN5cNKdFIZKFQ+qaBXBHLlz2CeCeyxgW9wk6bTXCdsZE0k1cBZLDvgsGzTIGW8yw9FVFenNwkiFReigAssdTa3vY1/77e6H0n9ZughC3C3KTYGP8Es2l5bnm77g7ZVLMyNluftIjSBWLwkgUF4k8J/cJJTjSm0DJ84YQqCEso8rvYTaIZlk8Q+gMR4Nwz3Xhc0un+OdINSwlDGNHx2PYBAzDoczJpXxspCCNYjJ21Z/rkzBHwIdqtyyTgp1JqyxHtjfLBkSDk+F22UvvQDg5b2/txvCPk3oswnj9+AKpA1BzT/HenvFSn4i65b+H2Msu/1gnmqMwtXEaX2NR4761FNhUHwpHrt3DatNw0AmCgD0i+vDqtn6MjrLeoghJescH6a9sKOf1oD5ujqJDgWayUc4r4N3fzGRX00e/KOKjR84U+icwCCzIjpye3IuCTkY6cn2CqAb8BHhB12ltzT2ry6Fv2pugGo5nH9jPwjB+/dgWqex5HiAmWHZEUy7k7wXUHVV48iveaMYH0MhnlemiO2tK8nVqqTsSh4NbfzhoR4CrcczynZ8xUVMv4dSFapZ14z0wVcq10Lg0zNU/cgGJlPbnYxwVMr2azhcPxYOFnWMZd/MpHLFZ9kmaHsFqy7aigtg8xTb/ppcKjuCFHuIaRFDZw9LAqwhJIwlcishlv87LbY9LJxyyjhFZYh5kxjGyrEo4VF9HogbSREZ0SHeK0T4FTUpKV27kVgZ2uyj6TgGIwsNiLqmAR+w9qcMuSjhJSltc0WhbysR+h2sunWpwF7/5ut8G03V21x0/ZENVwemTxIGuvi08lmmufQ9cmggYveLDkF7wAB4GJtcqZJAtcL3IV2Xm27PSyS0mHw6QHJkJqHq3ao0/z6WIsPfjmvMsDIw52m/GUIi/PGWbwHiw2bFXPQM7+MIZILraNDW/4OljTdwkLb+qmiku8N39WZBnjY7oO6QMd1hjoT6Tv+G8vQF6Agm7kOkI3MFVxbsEgrmAjcAi294tjZ6769VhIgRewEA2bfLxdqT/IeS+wKXG+NzHfaTyKfu6XAgf1ktuJ519hJnJ7i9bFStkALSFE4jVgoL7YT109Thsw32cCiDWX4X9VxXXYRb8Y4G0y"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11038","langCode":"en","question":"l22a7sBMwUT/uxJhiSI68/IYBb/A++sDeRTWGlPfbI6QZ8a2m43oCBChcsOmu3X3hTzabzrueonCJkpsyV337d5uPjpB8X/L9buzpqxXfF0mD56VKfpF2c9Pk08ehAu3Czb9/llKAa/UmMYmxYyD1B3+Kdvn+CUuUYW5oox2Dq8KzTM4jbNvwvXcd/vnhPtk","answers":["won","had won","have won","has won"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x18Ng9Qp5dPj3PrLftvnpM4CzFcERVJ1eHvSTCp0d+jfgI+lC49wnjNwabL++x/Ado/T6oCArAgxtV/d22IIB4Z+1lXzQxIEGe/TxIEk2hCO3WAy5B0+bwYOTKKFEQF3iTRjupIafeczKEcPG5eQps10ISyjyu9hNohmWTxD6AxHg5Wa0fOE7XJoxRahYvOHXYuuzi41PhtqpXaCTeHqBc6pTf6blZijLjnvRWYMml4sSbBAbTduAfu4QyFBA2TE5FICTBpKaEDMo+N3gJBqXk6d3zbyx8wuia1aFfW0c4f0L3G8+uipAvh2qTvQzZc8HICrnZaKe6izDUFYg+PX7NsyONZOcPtG2BKMLpF1WKyMJ5F/asmP8yGEi5vpj2acUNxxaVtW4duGoQsxkyur8xkDj0gbLg7zRuWBHkzq/CLp0P8s+MIuqIIa/zh1LY4lkxR6IQe3hwSX61sxMnbxETupL7MTfeL1mneMX7gYiFy4MAWjnt5INYdi6U43vDuQlM/xupCKpPWwmVuP5rHAad+PHn1brP1XGdk1zO0/3PdDCyUjc3O5XNASKF1gV3EX4GegAdugKH7jEMNEv5PEDTApripdQzBnBpO33GYrxcbh1cRG8V4qXWbcH7mlACnOkCBgPGerPTLeQcZ7CX+vDuiX8PwA+61005Mx+JiqKgioJzPKLpc2VMgBR2Y37sVOILg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11039","langCode":"en","question":"ryDtlknhdqAW/CuCULhf8el9/CEaDbhWnQ3P4ZjVKaSW/K1JxGB7N3Ri9VIGLupKfpHI1sp1IJGAZv0O5qHRaHGq0/Eaq29IN6y1pGtLNvr5dan1pvuJOf6RePZLL7uRwOUMaUhidSpI+tVg3X8q0PKCAz8KApLSZYLnHfpLsxU\u003d","answers":["had been working","have worked","have been working","has been working"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"1nNWOMQhR15WEOEOzLieQ65hMsBDvQfhy9/nazF8a3qPDTxVntiv//sHRONn5xusDFWBGrLOq4VuWQIAgewQ6raizhLpW57hcEx7Sy85B4WerQZuiBi4cmedWPftHNyk0KSu5F7eeHa1qflA6d2oS+mszz+YSYJ6b1c86qHBvncspA+icIAZc25Rt/6WABhDPiABe4dWmPv5aF0794wYrFlrzsGervxURBrojpX6I2CXzDlTMyKxlffH6fk5HQeZj6oU1leEVWxCgxu1GHE/LTqFZjx853BWbaKkFQFG72Cx8OqI6WjLl+jIucV2yrsX0w1wtWxlvrqjbLehLQx3i/b1UMcHBqFlalX6rx87ps70LdwR1jaeoF35hTn1AKmMl9p7aqPZH/dWYcWN+GvJg1Bv4msEWWeN4G9uBV6uSOvJhY6BtFd47ZepiGrdDAmkl8w5UzMisZX3x+n5OR0HmSKd04xxNmfrtY06g/Jr9+v6S6XpkS6ToW98jBz8DyL3HhACSKlgFan1NURoNi6HdQjTQQvsBWq1ijZDAHK0wQvj4Sl2y39x1sjV0pW9+W/dwygrTLbj8H8auSzQ+HUPGLXeuVFGsJZbYD0YnIxwyHt+ezEQjjFQJOkLih3KpwE5PPGqDhZtJOwggGXQ4tju+We+bOPSJtqPKoayn9o2Pb6NPup1nBbp5FMke2XnmIBtC0bGO0/KxhRdxoEzEqhVKBDghymzNsq3k2M+RIeYj0obO5f/kocSlMKvwKfL8Rm99HJm2pw9xRyN4ZmC9kyngQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11040","langCode":"en","question":"pef4kqxX3FHVuuQsBXYFv0slklggpm+15CE1I21CuEXaycNSGDHxwzIj053LlGIo","answers":["have been raining","was raining","had been raining","has been raining"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1wlrychWJqb50LYQLT/d67Z84skk3OylggcL8ZqzNA7n0uY666OHyvALFbrknZWPfgllVlzIt9H/evoekfcOtKm93L8wge2wVX/lSP9HEhSytZV80MSBBnv08SBJNoQjt6ksbp88eGqxK0/DwPU4yobh7rIm828qrGy0Ut7bYQoAOygFEVwIGDeI9oxJrW5otdnyav/e0SStZfxEAplpm3ynCf9CBSJ2W+RRgb8CTP6Ag7npWwaghkkh9N8rocysSlN/puVmKMuOe9FZgyaXixJ2VGLRfaU1HrJ7CsUpnF/wV3PMqmQL6zMRRUDU0fYCRhfaxVdcpD9Xhs+2Vp65btrZ2jeWbXcdhqQxD4byqlwmwNRV1iftIikO9zGG4FaAyyy8Jfx2jAWTegy5sAbCW8XMxz6eNL1I0yhTt7NbOtjJpwn/QgUidlvkUYG/Akz+gDYFqZSqdlitteqlrwughgiuJlytI4daNyRl0kj37Ed6k7mom0oLlajzQD0iyAhi8/MZ+EYrTFT1lZAUOfOppihCRZOAGPiQvzf2qcirH+3P1fzsXG0kIXX1EDhkvna0gCEm/8hajDeyhUYHPJs1ocR/DIHeo9kVLTvhFKC06A9Ru6Gqt+nAskmMww0r4GMcsMkOR78kJlAG+ngdQyvacnmUOLpLp9uZWw7hHqsOyqB/jIXcS1gW9Mjl8Rd+IG0/57TT5Jswqtt+L69xAmut0BnWV6xkK9vpL+9qlQlWEOVcnJFjwMWpx1fBEY8iYjY+Gw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11041","langCode":"en","question":"ekOYs3fSJPBfn5XpgJaGNfi+pBSFGCFQ+DdSjJYDqPriQzDSPSmeRM+W1hQnrfMPobS1odyLa68hbbkAbxVQzQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["has been putting","have been putting","were putting","had been putting"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"haymPDckd+aWWvS4OcPuBc6AJxlmN5cNKdFIZKFQ+qZLExT2HFRsJ0RzCjiXniGHhjaJ6qmIr+QN1mDFcpZ+ELUCoI4mIllnGszPiAdpk4KdkoHkx31zMgxbfZKvqVH7sDErZJxpR6WWRkD5h1wI9ykdKOxgJUYPCYQFCiEOF0VJkRrlNM/9ViRURVApBHsU/sYEsDqfmm4SVBItEZeTrDeZIsw5xrJITsNXDfUQ43wgeId5uWoXgieCsbmK6QHIud/kvt/U8a1hMWQHkMOyuNwz3Xhc0un+OdINSwlDGNFlVt49DsQjqXzRc+r3t1S/6EoJ+XlQk1YwbRN3cdIJUlcVhhgUm63cAcaK57PX9RlBNONtOGQtP39gfEYpqJJ5RfbnN6Bog2II78oXCoNCImAhQFZPU7yjFF07galGGCVr/GWi8sVC+H3FBoppeKqnQTDJKxhx6a/k34K3dSDbeW8emudaB9goKB6mgFWxbJN18CGVlLMBuaWXa6PZ8+158VpHaVeFPp+WQyKPaiZEn0WjHwBd5BIKmjY/hj3E3XVqzelsyzpZsFYXnVXksbjh4NiFxtoETwbYHGfopJL+jcpE8bK5qqJZiWAwRPNnku3OMc0S5F3ikjqC4KQ7cbIktW4lhlZ6HhxVBttZTg3r1+It4gDkpQbRt48bY2be+enTfkchVvzIMjkVufbYSTZ/YG4fsdntY48eF2P7A2ViPr8RjsixXDhurOI3w9RivQn19F31q4NmsWvxpW01mc2HCkGYH0a23QuSy/ggU15Zmxz95F62u5b//y7G/+xyY/o\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11042","langCode":"en","question":"rO6SnoSSr6F24wEC1wnAcCQ8vQWG6WCPceorqTYEbaRy723icIG5AO7h57wkRR9U4fUnoEkK4Rj1jaJBqfyx0OMepodorFUEhX4M7hpw3W4\u003d","answers":["were playing","have been playing","has been playing","had been playing"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1wlrychWJqb50LYQLT/d67Z6YCnPDN0QgHXWs3wLriiA0uY666OHyvALFbrknZWPfgllVlzIt9H/evoekfcOtKm93L8wge2wVX/lSP9HEhSytZV80MSBBnv08SBJNoQjt6ksbp88eGqxK0/DwPU4yobh7rIm828qrGy0Ut7bYQoAOygFEVwIGDeI9oxJrW5otQhLKPK72E2iGZZPEPoDEeBoE6EgpNs9VB+KFjYXyYU92IVT7HZL/sI8YGmqJuKoDUc5W105SShqn8LPlgxhpQ0HtwQtDftABay5YcRI/PXxXcpJzez2QTrIhmd5wlLOVvPNdskaN8CGetkWra76UMcnSdL2LBd1vJ7TuNrCpoY8HT8BT6H7dW4/KJZxEvbAnAZqQWJ1YQ4+eVPKwx0yO0NXE8hFjHwlVLG7tumEqXB4JEpAU40RYcVLda5vHbRIQNiFU+x2S/7CPGBpqibiqA3qpKaieqlB3cyaCGxx3vcFgNgR5Fus9LJZrxOakj3IXF3E5o8EzooA42FcZnlfqIStyJMd1ETgoag7oczhwztPBYrmtc7rsTSbbZLWiFJA/qgFK9rEOtN4tQ3qn83h4tqB2X9HO4EB6GLzgoIY2O9D8xGVNLYDjlEtz95t7gT3fCoii4AGRQL0yFTWJyb3avhtotWiW3i6PL+GJ+8R4KQGqWt24OGY+lTkavGcigli0R7R4YvI5/0TtZeewZ2yxWzmV+Vxro5sDxTx7CgDY+cNOnn+FHxfYcFR9Gd+oHx8qw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11043","langCode":"en","question":"YbDTK0QESYplD8WDKS/8WyOyvwTsShjF2Co5r82N/Zt9Kkj0AYhB81HcIPU8VGvYG0KPx+T78NmLVUIDedqleQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["had been working","was working","worked","has been working"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1wlrychWJqb50LYQLT/d67aSx1me/hueUiVjRwVfIIi20uY666OHyvALFbrknZWPfgllVlzIt9H/evoekfcOtKm93L8wge2wVX/lSP9HEhSytZV80MSBBnv08SBJNoQjt6ksbp88eGqxK0/DwPU4yobh7rIm828qrGy0Ut7bYQoAOygFEVwIGDeI9oxJrW5otQhLKPK72E2iGZZPEPoDEeAeFo73qI21ccOKCg/A5o6etJvOskLDY8PPjBgzVTUWLEb/zgyorc/4dFB42FmrbB2gE4rY5BQ8fEpq4x8F6plBNJq55BdWJDI1CunwY/SPmItPQDeS7RljaRSetF6BuRp7Ji48aWa1+sUPG39og/DdT1KN2wHABdKnNwmb8O1FYuPlD8kXIDCpJthR9mMaQjdZyb9VSvl3sP/Zrm/l5WhZOK7+fUO5e3EZqZbt6pV9c7SbzrJCw2PDz4wYM1U1FiyH3CM6iedBgnVStPdhVeuOktr1Rv88pNXhoT4zGAb0qojUBlyL8DuPd1ZxS2nbmvSBawgYV5d6Com+WwhIjGPPoo8yKGD3vGwhJB//6XP83wnWlDRe07ZR7ITj7LrkGPrnT/fuxjB7FAJmBPZF3B0SkgzRzEb12h0xBgEJ4d3oCCB1S7tYnvMCoV3gbwjm0DJhhrAh5Yrqyq1qf5GnvZHes4Tz2YOnXgh/qa2MfjN+DAVwCaHXXVoeqEi2Q5P3g/HAkXG2svXzin7BBwG1oTyZ2AJkaq1qhQ8XOCMk1a88Pw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11044","langCode":"en","question":"ppW1Ukayz/+oq8hMGOGD1kwoSDqvIaFEu9j1fTjsIuc\u003d","answers":["has been jogging","had been jogging","jogged","was jogging"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1wlrychWJqb50LYQLT/d67auFS1f9ps7nXD3ae/URRCo0uY666OHyvALFbrknZWPfgllVlzIt9H/evoekfcOtKm93L8wge2wVX/lSP9HEhSytZV80MSBBnv08SBJNoQjt6ksbp88eGqxK0/DwPU4yobh7rIm828qrGy0Ut7bYQoAOygFEVwIGDeI9oxJrW5otQhLKPK72E2iGZZPEPoDEeBihJcEG2HI54y9Cq065DldISSzRCMPWjvBlptI2VyaWo22aNtvDM9A+pdYgBuWPvhqH6FuafoWUQYvbsOP7U6UGGmvKvOVntZXI76iPRGlIa8LcF3PP8OlmUHAHRE9XSI+zvL/ZPzVpSzYTE/pUY7n3JpNOb1L2q0zWLb3ucfP2sAYOFd4lUhEtJLpCCz0RV5dyknN7PZBOsiGZ3nCUs5WEuIyICEdAiAbs/IclFiI5CEks0QjD1o7wZabSNlcmlqMH792Bap7HkeICZYdkRTLhOG/mF0dZ/YURJnbTivaBlFaDEOvRIdmh1HTUWzCXGsyfK0RcUioqiIOm1elNEko0n+gVI0yZV1CSVWqGGtJqzRH0QnRugKFWNWh/iT1Pvu7Vs+rlNRSur3e1G/QSMR2qQxSN8dv20rwag5WOg7quovzgSQghdnwpQgTAStRVtb11GE3HYmd+iHSdtFD8TiWfwyB3qPZFS074RSgtOgPUZi68aItkVgifMajzBwiTK0r1fAGKU7H6dIoIyupeSb8E2j0kn3i5cVkRtuCDh/SaA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11045","langCode":"en","question":"2sJ8QLZ+raU55ueTaZW089HhGRzAFetUuBEPabMVDgcGv5s1XGO/yA4iIe4Ud5LeVIC+wjrbN5po07yMmxwOEQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["worked","was working","has been working","had been working"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1wlrychWJqb50LYQLT/d67aSx1me/hueUiVjRwVfIIi20uY666OHyvALFbrknZWPfgllVlzIt9H/evoekfcOtKm93L8wge2wVX/lSP9HEhSytZV80MSBBnv08SBJNoQjt6ksbp88eGqxK0/DwPU4yobh7rIm828qrGy0Ut7bYQoAOygFEVwIGDeI9oxJrW5otQhLKPK72E2iGZZPEPoDEeCQybFOG8jr4IryKeSMXvMSjddmhI8D3dlNv2qOJQ+8w/J/OlQEewIxbhgITQnYEMmFbeg+xEJkD5FgKy7PmIyFvYrVNiQ1lrPoGJSctIufHfMnPMQgmBNGPqaTN2sgiVEQBe4w3CqkQKXHJ4edqJ7XMfSEUvxjOOCZVw1/EJUr7gHI8nLSeHCDT/ADdZOzhsmIvKB0MwJ8XItCxnyB0HarFjY3rX8XAB6RzHghbZrEV43XZoSPA93ZTb9qjiUPvMOS7TRsrMlxkWNtjYrac1DjxQPruq0bA15Mmni/fCrHns7pvuRsBOLK4pOXisbfWmNVFy2+XILxxj5o+agF50+ICZTE5U9PKrpQaXRqSxXdAosr55AZH4pnzrMoHpIw9cH1fhtJVJEMlRy2re3xeWuZua9QYZVnNle+CRzqAG5fMA1mT1yxjF3zUT13OHz6FvAbO5f/kocSlMKvwKfL8Rm9x59W6z9VxnZNcztP9z3QwpDwdNB1AiU3elFt4I2g5itcJq/0YDSDrtJcDJC3qhm1XJDvnxfpXpoWAU5OaxvQYA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11046","langCode":"en","question":"XNLmgyZB29p8rb+dV2R0TOhUss+1W3wYgxxOQhf6XfcW8FGfLF/8AH6qshvFj+0346xti0QWxleWZn+LeX5g0w\u003d\u003d","answers":["have been looking","has been looking","looked","had been looking"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"fbYUV1ZLKlcp62xprJGr3LNUgARA7StsqyonUT7vO3jKdjhPjXbbAhaHmsaLAmRy9NOhk6upXU673s5uAYscP+ryGsimHLARcbtnSH7FwAm/qUzbuP4C4QCv0qNMrACRmNUOCag/+8jLhQequ4eE4m2qNtJfZIt3Rbc/J1wz+B2y5KYj0psMf4/yFoaFHn7vnmvQ5zMU87iGKffqSytUxyFWRaqKhH1Aus+giPjIDj3+5WMnoEQM6LG/J4w+aZQl4dEQW0HAaNAz59ElWjt3reryGsimHLARcbtnSH7FwAldX0JmXuQCoC/d38/H21jpU9HGAlovsgPHP5s80sAVGghLKPK72E2iGZZPEPoDEeD8MG3CUjkBk362TX/LGQI361HQMHeg82GgaH9qz3+okyGl7cuN4gvkPe9JaeGnUZMi1f8pmUv7/Segc1nAJ9Ut0MxVF2SSOQKkCkLwbmOyVyyfxCtkRdOHaj1vVPXjsn7KIeL1b5hGUMj5wbp7Xs0vkK1Nsx6M7fgLIWb0hW/dCNn+zkSjiIrFRPH15iPLv9Xow334Mh6NpM89U80BlHzP/R9BDhVQrm9OSaWysJA1vOtR0DB3oPNhoGh/as9/qJOuQZzfCH5LVGPwcpgbbe5us4ULs1Smr9OSA+ZxNBr7gT1XcQaNNDK4mAy20Vc2Mr9ByIfGF9YowShc78Ygeub0Wm8FUvNevnaAefFjzKRDfwuBghMd0qdo0A3hxzzidDIdLiCcb/uMi7f62+xVQkw1hh40bMI1uI4Va+qVwQx5ZiFWRaqKhH1Aus+giPjIDj3+5WMnoEQM6LG/J4w+aZQlzhoR4CrcczynZ8xUVMv4dVEgLPOJE4A5sNM2Ghv67Ww9zapfMO46A6nYDZDrrdjs38fvbX0bvQCbp9XzE7wIpg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11047","langCode":"en","question":"mEmCn8zzh5OOZwTFN7sL0AgBM2QA2h1BbdvGmYgKc7nydoYvSQ21nw2hQAdeio3ihrifCnI+yVHUE57PTenduA\u003d\u003d","answers":["was living","lived","has been living","had been living"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1wlrychWJqb50LYQLT/d67bqkcr4XQeXICZCjJ8Yoh7v2TDwdlzsA8Mzgm8c6wNz70aaEUwQPtDFJCEUDonHL421FYIxxd4sjmAIUQ95HMcvPg/X+YRoyLlQzDvTce0rBi1BwMp4TdpGFjNOCZU3STcq8a5EcFhnHYPpugonlh7dSdZGhiC6x/fyuw043n9DMB7qqyerqo14nAX57Z6pO1GSWO6iYQevYCd8BvCU5XvoObqbazz6cYnEjGqsTfFGK5IV+rYyfdyFvl9FTOWDKkm6XmgrIH07vUn7j2W8nlv3dX8WhFrjF6M+0cAj7wIke5hw3AyFoAzyxIiEBDFFZzaig8uKmGKoM6K1nuzQ4xH486NluM9iQ+KYbBv2HdcE/MCUCeUHjJN4yqyGxAR538ziJlFNfQGior4xvi8viCSFkljuomEHr2AnfAbwlOV76OPLWF/ioxjwMGSPl2NcHwYllosMeJmBjS7V41/U3tf2S3RmuMcJHW9Af+c2ujACBvFDvB5rG8RZa/GcWDPcVCPNecoyluwjFO7rrXbXscdPw7Z+KrMDv3fPML90q+/+7KYGVnAMjDRWNSF3CuorvyaTxlrblFbc3hxBsZb0NCbyYhQZrpd9+OtdF2EyZTvBeCxZ60p6LoPAup8NPFlDg2rah0tZ774wz39We68W6oGy8BAxbCAIZBqOYCMPE7xsqLLBKc8Z1IbgkMqIHGAwjGeNPup1nBbp5FMke2XnmIBtzPKLpc2VMgBR2Y37sVOILg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11048","langCode":"en","question":"tr65LuA4rrcKS+f2WtvUAv78jkPSAk1hpacPxloJBmXGLxAq5DRHNbgvMeg96Sxq","answers":["hears","had heard","have heard","heard"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1/blOkoSALe2mbevLvhLI7I5lm6BHt0ck4HbJnGfYKc0WfFMNbRPZTx/daUv1fBduFqXzN/WUmD74jiumSpoAtv7Pi4j6/E6SKcBq3jUxcZMN3TTXnAlzhVoYhkzqaOZVzuh9eG6Au6tp41wsPVUlvMISyjyu9hNohmWTxD6AxHgCEso8rvYTaIZlk8Q+gMR4I81JTBGe63b+0w8JZKJ92/oSgn5eVCTVjBtE3dx0glSHi6EU7/GLLq6+bavAXpeBv53AlkWyNUJpNAl9rhp+VNa5Pftan1i4FIzdRJrAilDhBYFvSkQoFHs+zAyjiy1EimcrRSFh6ESKBp4aWaTOSlrK7G+i0pXtYIw86FL7oztHp1kKTnoi6IGP6r9+wvCTOkCKgjJBXXjZbPVTTDKYZNiEEC+BwA13sPgyLdu3RfhCLcc+hqv9z66TR3w6sRbkAe7xaxAMPwcZwjrCR1uWzucHK5qxzpK65XzWD/ffr6k6eoqIEN4AoT7gY3Yhf18pdxpQERg1kE2R1B0QWT8NG7hk+pcXCqK1COeS2lMpFfBRrPDtGXWbeQcenNZyg8Mfhi29h8o2Y22xU9dUf1/g/PxckYwcujoGolwz9qa9zsPnVlnhyPL2NtRVftJHspuHaHA5/2QIPmY1CvMbCcNNgR9owoGl+xQgen0C70OtCz5E2j0kn3i5cVkRtuCDh/SaA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"11","id":"11049","langCode":"en","question":"WVI+0J3S3gMuWsRitRejOg2UvtfceuqDCQ2az8YK5zgcwEAsXskcBBDrPmDkhZtRrkS1rC8QJ69UVxWs9d8osA\u003d\u003d","answers":["has been explaining","explains","explained","had been explaining"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1wlrychWJqb50LYQLT/d67alP6tbHJmVwVvxB0vWU6Tqu6Gqt+nAskmMww0r4GMcsMkOR78kJlAG+ngdQyvacnmUOLpLp9uZWw7hHqsOyqB/4qyaAqE5kMP22UWfPCJlUxnpyEfoEsfZ8IlT9ZRPWbRhLr5fGG2wts9uaOksIfsyJVxebgPbGuWkBcM8GUuzHAhLKPK72E2iGZZPEPoDEeDMP3vz2qY2t4QxjLSf2cTCtIvJwY28cdyi1gPfDN36+U/acu8uaZvvcW7CL7ioYeXosnnHIRGUyb/rhiKk794DWhB5fawUN2GENF+UHuRctmJFgmvyrIs6lP5yItxl8frbvup88eDkL2oRljobz01P9ahEEs0UrP8RwMIZcxxhb4QWBb0pEKBR7PswMo4stRLZn7S1TUyJjd+vCX1n1036uVLlFukH1UyVNCkaC4rRELSLycGNvHHcotYD3wzd+vkQwiD8UkBokwD2Rr0fSmTVZaNcnJsFr8urb7U1bOmoPuQjj42nyDr78BnV0TKOMYBrslul4UsPdsOAdSlImZKWygl/qkx2ZHoOuNDsW1NxGqHeLFEJCF97oz49k6DVz+j60OIv1axB2lDDJxFZ8V+9MMkrU69UQ2hv0G8ukZGtjeCbOI6hhIuekMD0cPVIdPJQBJdHarPTCComi6f60eXFk8Za25RW3N4cQbGW9DQm8gpj3+1z3OQmU6ZoH1TpzLG+Soh1WmZyGnW8gyQjM5gTluzFN7Q5+l3gsrhgZ3JnHA\u003d\u003d"}]